Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
Can anybody recognize the song I was murmuring?
I think that's the wrong word for... you don't say murmurring.
The song I was not whistling.
You know when you go... fuck, what is the word for that?
Whatever.
However, I come bearing good news.
I have fixed the map situation.
Humming, that's it.
Thank you, Hayef.
What's up, everybody?
You know, I was looking into the whole... I felt so bad after the last time that I had to go through the whole map experience.
And I was looking into some advanced shit, you know, like a couple of things I tried.
The obvious thing was to try the automatic scene switcher in OBS that recognizes what window is active and then switches the scene.
But I had some problems with that.
It didn't always work for some reason and then it would switch when I didn't want it to.
And sometimes I have to Alt-Tab and then it switches anyway.
It's just annoying.
So I figured out the perfect solution.
Not only is the problem fixed, but the map experience is also enhanced.
It's even better now.
OK, so watch this.
This is it.
Get ready.
I'm in the game.
There, that's the game.
There it is.
OK, I'm in the game.
And then let's say I I'm going to draw something.
I go whoop.
OK, I made a box.
OK, fine.
That's cool.
I go back.
What you may not have noticed is that if I stay here for longer, I'm just going to stay here for a bit now, you will notice that maybe I'm drawing.
You know, I'm doing things like that.
Very slowly.
A beautiful melody plays fades in and
it's a melody that is very recognizable, at least to me.
And if I leave this open by accident, then I will know it's still open because the melody is playing.
It's basically like an inception where you know you're dreaming still because you hear the song.
OK, so when I hear that thing playing, I know to switch back and it only plays if I have it open for long enough.
And let's say I'm in here drawing a lot and the intention is to stay here a while.
Well, then we have some nice music to listen to at the same time.
The kick, exactly.
Let me get rid of these.
So that's it.
That's the solution.
And then I can simply go back and it's gone.
Easy peasy lemon squeezy.
I was thinking, man, at first I wanted to record my own voice going map, map, map.
I think people would lose their minds over that.
So I thought, OK, we got to get get something soothing and relaxing.
And of course, we got to go with that one song from Hollow Knight.
Oh, yeah, guys, I'm so excited because today we're continuing the God run.
My very first.
It's exciting.
I am smiling like an idiot right now, but I am ready to just die within five minutes and that's going to be OK because I've already gained so much knowledge.
I've learned so many things.
I don't even care at this point.
Whatever.
I don't even remember where I was.
I'm jumping in.
OK.
Let's see here.
What was I doing?
I think I came to a whole new world here and this is that.
I forgot exactly where I was.
Let's see.
I have seven thousand gold.
So look at this shit right here, guys.
This is so insane.
Like I was thinking about this stuff since last time, like when I was out biking, when I was, you know, chilling in the sun.
I was just thinking, holy crap, I am overpowered as fuck.
That shit is broken.
It's it's like essential.
It is so good.
So I have that one.
It's pretty good, but I could remove this actually, just because.
Well, I guess I still lose mana quite quick.
Man, what I really need, I really need and add mana.
That's what I need.
Hopefully I'll find it.
But anyway, the plan is to just fucking try and solve some puzzles and go deeper down the rabbit hole.
Last time I was completely fucked in the head after that long amount of playing and all the stuff that happened.
I can't tell you.
I was just I was high.
Basically, I couldn't focus on anything at the end.
It was just too much.
It was too insane.
But now I've calmed down.
Peplicate spell.
What the fuck does that mean?
To add pepper to it or can we also have a salt spell?
Quantum split.
That's really good, though, isn't it?
I don't want to spend my money.
It's too expensive.
I will just continue.
Look at this.
I have infinite healing.
I have infinite black holes.
This shit is broken.
Until I get polymorph'd.
The more I think about the polymorph situation, the more I'm scared.
My god, I do a lot of damage.
Wait, is the polymorph going on down there?
What's happening there?
Are you actually taking damage?
I guess you are, but it's like weird.
Also, I am in... Where actually am I right now?
I am in the art.
Or like the dark version of the art.
And I have... Do I have vampirism?
I do, but I don't really need it anymore.
Like, I have infinite healing.
I have to get used to that.
It's still not something I have gotten comfortable with yet.
It's too crazy.
But I do need money, and I actually am getting a lot of money here.
Especially because... Look at this.
I have this now.
You gain double the gold per nugget.
I also have telekinetic kick.
And then I did this last time, which was... I actually kind of forgot about that.
The celestial rage came down and dug the most giant hole that has ever been dug.
Actually beautiful.
Hello.
Bye bye.
Wait, I wonder if I am immune to that now, because I have melee immunity.
This is melee damage, right?
Come on, do the thing.
Do the thing.
Am I... Am I immune?
I can't tell.
I think I am.
I think that counts as melee damage.
Guys, I will not die today.
I can't die.
It's actually impossible.
Oh wait, I can't kill those guys, of course.
Look at all that gold.
Like, I don't even care about taking damage from them, because I can just go like bonk.
And I heal.
Man, I feel like my wand is way better than I remember.
Did I do something to it?
Hold on.
What did I do?
I guess it's just a really good wand I made.
Just seems more effective than I remember.
But, okay.
Alright.
Also, what is my last wand?
I don't have a last wand.
I need to make something crazy.
Boink.
Oh yeah, right.
I have this.
Forgot about that.
Telekinetic kick, bitches.
I need something to kill small animals like this, efficiently.
Some kind of really good area of effect.
AOE.
That's what I need.
And I'm immune.
Oh shit.
Fuck!
Hold on, what's going on?
I just see a bus.
Hold on, there's something going on.
Oh, fucking hell.
Amazing!
Okay, so, I don't know if I can explain this.
So, I have my OBS, right?
And it's basically a copy of what you guys are seeing on the screen.
So, the giant game with a little chat in the bottom right.
But the text is like so small that you can't really read it, right?
But I just see something go flying on the side and it's like something's going on here.
Thank you guys.
Thank you so much.
That actually worked.
I fucked up.
In fact, this may actually have done something that it shouldn't have.
Hold on.
I need to quickly go inside.
Wait a minute.
I gotta think.
Nah, it's probably okay.
There may be an issue with the music then in the drawing screen.
Let's just quickly test it.
I'm going over here.
Hopefully the music is not duplicated now.
Gonna have to let me know in a second here.
Oh, I guess there's also music in game.
That's gonna be weird.
Shit, I didn't think this through.
Ah, I see the issue.
Okay, yeah.
Damn it.
I thought I had it figured out.
That's okay, though.
We gotta have a new plan for this.
I'm switching back.
I have something I can fix, but I'm gonna do it while taking a break soon.
Not right now.
Uh oh, taking damage.
I can't believe I fucked it up that bad.
I had the most genius idea, but I didn't think it through.
I'm just checking the meters right now.
Okay, you should be able to hear everything now.
Oh, wait, I don't have water.
I have berserkio.
Ambrosia and concentrated mana.
All right.
Okay, good.
Okay, back on track.
Let's see here.
The question is, should I even be exploring that much here?
I mean, I guess I want the money.
It's not a bad idea.
What am I taking damage?
Huh?
Oh!
It's the surface.
It's cursed rock.
I didn't even notice.
My perception is negative today, guys.
It's not voting well.
It's not a good sign.
I do wonder if I can find more hearts here.
We have to try that.
Let's just go around a bit and see if we... There's a heart!
Never mind!
Oh, but wait, it's...
It doesn't give me a debuff, though.
The last time I got one, it gave me a debuff.
Weird.
Maybe it's just certain hearts.
What's up, himises?
I'm just going deeper.
Kill them all.
Whoops.
Okay, I need to try and pay attention to these enemies, by the way.
Some of them polymorph, and I need to know exactly what they look like.
It's kind of hard to know without testing it, I guess.
I was like, I keep forgetting.
I can just make holes!
This new power I have is mind-bogglingly insane.
Okay, so that guy... Oh, I did.
Yeah, okay, he's already dead.
I guess I can just go in here.
I don't care.
I don't care about damage, because I can just heal.
How broken is that?
So, those are blue balls.
Wait, why am I taking damage?
Oh, I'm toxic sludged, I see.
Oh, my screen is very red.
I really love telekinetic kick.
I feel like I'm starting to play a little more careless, just because I can heal so much.
Maybe that's a mistake.
I mean, I can afford to play a little more careless, just not too much.
I'm doing a good amount of damage here.
Ooh, that's bad.
Also, I forget what the red ones do.
Alright, they collapse things.
So, I'm full.
So, I am melee immune, I'm fire immune, and I'm explosion immune.
How crazy of a combo is that?
I think it's mad.
Let's make a hole.
Oh, I'm stuck.
Dude, I can literally just make like a hole from the bottom to the top all the way, and just whenever I need to go all the way down, I just fall.
Similar to this one, Sadikivi.
I can do my own Sadikivi.
Okay, so that guy shoots blue balls.
He has a blue head.
Let's see what he does.
I'm taking the chance here.
Come on.
Shoot me.
Oh, it bounces.
Come on.
I'm not sure what it does.
Maybe it shouldn't experiment like this.
It's a bit scary.
Wait, what happened here?
Oh, a worm died.
Look at that.
What I should do is put a light on the black hole too, so I can see where it goes.
Okay, this guy.
That guy.
Already at 16k.
I'm gaining money fast here.
Wait a minute.
What happens if I... Oh, I should probably not go through the portal, right?
That's like the big deal.
Don't go through the portal.
Don't even do it.
Uh-oh.
Wait, what?
Huh?
I must have got teleported.
I have no idea what just happened.
I must have hit some teleportation.
Down, down, down, down, down, down.
Oh, I'm so slow.
This is insane.
The black hole just went through everything.
Does not give a fuck.
Just... Wait, where am I right now?
Shouldn't there be a... something?
Hold on, I'm actually kind of lost.
Go up again?
Hmm.
So the portal is there.
I guess it should be right below, right?
So like this way?
Oh, there's a worm.
Wait, what is happening here?
Huh?
East Volcanic Lake.
Where's the... where are the perks?
Show me the perks.
Sir?
Maybe this way.
Why is there a divider?
Dude, I already got the pooping feeling.
And it's not even like 10 minutes into gameplay.
I don't want to teleport through these.
I'm too scared.
I hear lava?
So I have a question.
Does the black hole eat through anything?
You know?
Is there something in this world where even the black hole does not work?
Wait a minute.
I don't understand where I'm going.
Did I hear something?
Wait, I hear something.
Oh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, make a hole for that.
Oh, shit, this guy's in the way now.
Oh, crap.
Oh, oh, oh.
Okay, I am so lost.
I have no clue where to... what the... hello!
Y'all can also shoot black holes.
Am I... I'm not immune to lava.
All right.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, what's happening here?
Entered east?
The labyrinth?
What a weird... Oh, shit.
What the fuck
is this place?
I am so confused.
Hey.
Okay, so the blue guy is the teleport man.
Okay, that's good to know.
So when you shoot him, you switch places.
And this guy is... what do you do?
Come on.
I can't... my shield is too good.
Honestly, this shield is kind of insane.
I guess I'll test it in the next run when I don't have the shield on.
Because I need to know exactly what these enemies do.
Oh, something got destroyed over there.
Come on.
Yo, what is happening?
This looks like a bug, guys.
It looks like that same problem I had when my world got corrupted, remember?
Hold on, I'm actually gonna ask you guys, is this actually a bug?
I'm just gonna ask this.
So this totally looks broken to me as if the world is corrupted.
It's not a bug.
Okay, cool.
Okay, but that's weird then.
All right, thanks.
It's not a... that totally looks like a bug.
But okay, I mean, I gotta say this game is a little bit janky though in certain aspects.
So okay, I guess to be expected.
But okay, if it's not a bug,
just a bunch of lava.
Wait, what's happening here?
Hold on, I gotta recharge my... what the...
What?
Guys, I am so deep down the rabbit hole.
I have no clue what's going on.
This is awesome.
I'm just going wherever the fuck this black hole takes me.
Okay, I need to teleport through these.
This is actually kind of annoying.
It's weird that it makes these, like, grooves.
Like this.
I wonder why it does that.
Am I hearing something?
East magical temple.
It feels gloomy in here.
Okay, sure, let's...
Oh, hello there, sir.
I have no idea where I am on the map.
And it's absolutely impossible for me to try to map this right now.
I'm just going... I'm just going.
I'm just experiencing this.
There's almost no enemies here.
It's too damn dark.
There's that sand.
What's up, fools?
East wizard's den.
Okay,
yeah, so the blue one is the teleport guy.
Confirmed.
Oh, you know what?
It's totally colors.
Blue is like teleportation.
So, polymorph's got to be pink, I guess.
It actually kind of makes sense.
There's also a green one, which got to be... What is green?
Acid?
What is green?
Acceleration or something?
I'm actually not sure.
Oh, wait a minute.
There's this weird cloud here.
Make a hole.
That guy is... I think he's electricity.
He was like sparking or sparkling.
And this guy right here is... electricity, I think.
Like, these guys can be different things based on the symbol they have above their head.
Hey, stop it.
Whoever that was, I killed him.
Bro, I feel like this toxic sludge is... I need some water.
Wait a minute.
Oh, I'm missing a wand.
I thought I had an extra slot there, but I don't.
It's too damn dark in here.
Oh, what was that?
Who's that?
Ah, you're down.
Okay, you know what?
I kind of want to go up here.
East desert.
Shit.
Okay,
you know what?
I'm going to do something here.
I refuse to believe I can't get those damn perks.
So here's the plan.
I'm going to go through the portal and see what happens.
Because maybe it's different.
This is like the last portal, right?
Teleport, teleport, just go through.
Just make a giant fucking hole.
But be careful.
Some crazy shit could happen.
This is so weird.
I've never had this power of just being able to go wherever I want.
And now I'm back in this weird, layered, dense brick... brickworked place.
Wait, I've been here.
Oh, I'm here now.
Okay.
So I need to go down now.
I do wish that fucking message would stop appearing.
Like, you don't have to give me a shock to tell me everything is okay.
It's like the tax man coming in and being like, boom, you paid your taxes on time.
Like, okay, okay, cool.
I know.
You don't need to yell.
Give me this.
What the hell just happened there?
The green one is... the curse.
Oh my god, I'm getting so rich.
Whoo!
What's that?
Invisiblium.
Maybe I want that.
Or maybe I don't.
Actually, I do.
I don't want this.
I want Invisiblium.
Thank you.
Oh no.
The scary thing about this black hole is that it goes so fast and so quick.
And far.
And sometimes you don't want it to go that far, but it does.
Okay.
Fly upwards.
No, I mean, I don't have a wand anyway, so why not just take it?
I'll replace it.
Right?
So that guy is... wait, what?
He just got... polymorph, though.
Oh no.
Wait, okay, so maybe it's not based on the color.
Shit.
How did he just get... polymorph?
Dude, that guy has a lot of HP.
I take it back.
This one is not that great.
Okay.
Holy crap.
A thousand gold!
Yo.
I think I found one of those before in this same run.
Oi!
Okay.
Okay, so here's the thing.
Obviously, last time I saw this portal, I was like, okay, straight down.
But there are multiple of these portals, right?
So we gotta find the right one.
So...
We just gotta try, all of them.
So straight down.
Wow, this is actually the same one I was in before.
Okay.
Let's go left them.
Okay, so there's one here.
Also, there's a thing up here.
What's that?
A bunch of holy lances.
I gotta be on the lookout for just really good wands as well.
Point one...
It's not a bad wand.
That's actually a really good wand.
But no.
I shall say no to that.
Was that a worm?
I thought I saw a worm.
Straight down.
Okay, so it's not here.
It's gotta be the next one then.
Or the next one after that.
Come on, guys.
Okay, straight down.
Huh.
It's not that one either.
Gotta be the next one.
Dude, I'm getting so much gold.
This green perk is actually wild.
Wait, I have tried this though.
Let's just do it for complete mistake.
There's nothing.
I guess I tried this one too.
Worm meat?
Wait, this actually looks kinda...
No.
Wow, okay, so it's not here.
Alright.
Take the portal.
Yeah, look at this.
Now I'm right below the moon.
Okay.
Alright, that's cool.
Did I ever take the...
perk in the very last?
Oh, I guess I did, because that's here.
What happens if I...
Oh, I already did go up here.
Also, do I want any of these spells?
Let's see.
I don't know where to go.
What's that one?
Circle of Buoyancy.
I actually kinda like that.
Liquid detonation sounds cool.
Okay, so, oh, right, right, right, this is what I want to do.
So there's east, there's gotta be west.
That's my plan.
We're going west now.
We gotta get to the bottom of this.
Go up.
And then I actually want to go back to the meat realm as well.
Because now that I have so much healing, I mean, come on.
Oh.
What's happening?
Up, up, up.
In fact, I never explored this place fully.
You may as well do that.
Projectile, oh, hold on, what was this again?
If a valid target appears somewhere in the proximity of a projectile, the projectile will teleport right on top of the target.
I mean, that seems kinda cool.
But is that gonna prioritize me if there's no targets?
That's the thing I'm worried about.
I should try it.
For science.
Yeah, I think it did exactly that.
So let me try now.
Oh!
Wow, okay.
Let me try on an enemy.
Enemy?
Mother... this is a death warrant.
Uh-oh.
Bad idea.
I don't enjoy that want.
Like, why did it not prioritize the damn enemy?
Get him.
Yeah, I'm just gonna keep exploring here for a bit.
Maybe I'll find, um...
some ad mana.
Right?
That's like the big one.
So that guy bleeds...
I think.
Was that freezing vapor or is it teleportation?
That is...
Why won't it tell me?
Like, mousing over it.
It won't say.
Whatever.
Uh-oh, that's the teleport guy.
Oi!
A worm!
A spectral worm.
I can't take damage.
Oh my god, so much gold.
Oish!
Reduce lifetime.
That could be...
nice, actually, on the black hole.
Because you get the speed from the black hole, but you don't make it go as far.
Right?
And sometimes you don't want to make it go that far.
You want to be more precise with it.
Stop it.
The good news is, I killed these guys pretty fast now.
Oh, why is it so much cursed here?
Not that I care.
Oh, there's a wand up here.
Jesus.
That's a lot of those.
Four guarding lights rotate around you for a time.
You know, maybe that is kind of cool.
Hold
on.
Huh.
Guarding lights.
Like, it doesn't absorb, I don't think.
But it damages enemies.
Wait, someone's buffing.
Uh-oh.
Oh no!
Oh wait, I'm on their side now.
They won't attack me because I'm on their side.
Day 63, they don't suspect a thing.
Fucking idiots.
Oh yeah.
Nothing can hurt me.
I like doing this.
This looks really nice, it's like firework.
Look at that, it actually lasts a long time too.
Imagine you get a wand that shoots like ten projectiles at once.
Or you make it so that you always shoot like a million of these.
You always activate it.
And then you're always safe in melee distance.
You know?
That could be kind of dope.
What's that?
Chaotic polymorphine.
I don't know if I want that.
Seems too chaotic for me.
A wand.
A big wand!
Whoa!
Concentrated ex...
Reduce spread is nice.
Only costs one mana.
I think I'm tempted.
Yep.
That's the one I want for now until I find something better.
To bring back to base.
Did that guy die or did he teleport?
Ah, nice!
Some HP for me.
Oh!
I didn't even see you there.
Okay.
In fact, how about I just go left?
I was like, oh, I want to go west so I'm going to go up first, but I don't have to do that.
I can just fucking black hole it!
I go straight line west now, no matter what comes across me.
Directly from here, baby.
Ah, wait.
Shit!
There we go.
Oh, hold on.
Wow!
Nice!
More HP is very welcome.
And even more!
What's happening?
This is like super lucky.
Did that guy just die from the other guy's projectile?
Amazing.
Okay, we keep digging.
1700 HP.
I've never had this much before.
Let's try and make it straight.
I'll make it crooked.
It's like there.
Weird how it sort of became wider.
Unless I shot two of them somehow.
Huh?
Wait, why is it...
Why is it splitting off like that?
Oh, hello!
Fucking hortus!
What are you doing out here?
And where am I?
Now we're suddenly in the snow.
You know what's nice?
This is like a little...
It's like a compass having this moon there.
You know sort of where you are on the map.
Not bad at all.
It points north.
Points straight up.
Uh oh, we got stuff following us.
This is just wild.
Where the fuck am I?
Please don't follow me.
Uh oh.
I have no idea what's going on.
Oh, don't do it.
I get no text.
Tell me where I am.
I think I need to be careful.
I can still die getting caught in like some electricity and shit.
Where I can't move.
If I'm stunned, that's bad.
So electricity and polymorph.
Those are the two main fears that I have at this point.
Oh, here we go.
Different terrain.
I am terrible at keeping this straight.
What the hell is this?
Have I been here?
What is happening?
I just keep going.
Ah!
I was stuck.
Okay, the lake.
Ooh.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh shit.
Uh oh.
This may be a bad idea.
Oh wait, it's actually giving me O2.
Aha!
It's removing the water.
I'm getting like a little bit of time to breathe.
Uh oh, uh oh.
Shit.
I have to remember, I have teleport.
Go!
This is crazy!
I feel like I'm doing something bad here.
It's a bad idea!
What the hell?
Shit.
Come on, come on.
Oh!
Holy fuck!
Huh?
Let me read this again.
Also, I need to take a picture of this.
Goes in my collection.
Here I'm safe.
I am safe.
I left the others behind and I have locked my research so that only those with real understanding can reach it.
I should not worry.
As long as I resist the temptation, I will be safe.
I know my limits.
Here, I am far away from them.
I should not worry.
Hmm.
Cheers.
Oh yeah.
So, we can bring a tablet here, remember?
And then a portal spawns.
But I don't have a tablet.
So, there's that.
But, I wanted to keep going west, so I'm doing it.
Fuck off.
Huh?
Oh wait, I remember something like this!
Oh no.
Tapion Vasali.
It's blocking.
I don't like this, guys.
I don't know how to do damage to it.
I'm leaving.
Nope, we're leaving.
Whatever the fuck that is, I'm out.
Bye-bye.
Did you see that?
It absorbed everything I did.
And I have no idea why.
Ah!
Ooh.
Fuck, I gave me a jump scare.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Oh, that was easy.
It wasn't even a problem.
West desert, baby.
I was right.
Do we have a west-west?
West watchtower.
Oh, wait a minute.
We gotta check if there's a different drawing in here.
Oh, and look how easy it's gonna be to get in now.
Oh, wait, wait, we don't wanna drain it completely.
Uh, wait.
Wait, I can actually see the drawing from here.
It's the same drawing.
Yeah.
That is definitely the pond.
And then something above it.
I don't remember if I ever did that.
Whoa!
I was up in the sky at one point.
This thing is also here.
What the fuck?
Oh, you know what?
We're gonna try going to the pyramid and see if the boss is there.
West pyramid.
So what does this mean?
This is definitely referring to the floating inverted pyramid thingies.
Right?
Kinda looks like it.
Also, do we have a...
Oh, look at this one.
Yeah, just keep healing.
Ah, this is totally fine.
The necessity of concealing the art is one of the chief anxieties of alchemists.
We are sworn to secrecy by heaven and earth and hell.
By the four elements.
The four elements.
By the height and the depth.
By Hermes, by Anubis, and by the howlings of Kirkros.
An oath has been required of us to reveal nothing clearly to any initiated being.
Who...
Who has been telling you...
Who has made that requirement, is what I'm asking?
The gods?
Whoops.
Oh no, come here.
Ah!
Wait, I can't pick it up anyway.
Ah, rip.
I took a picture of it though.
I had my phone out.
So here we can definitely do this.
Oh!
That does not work here.
Interesting.
Okay.
What if I dig right down?
Sup fool?
Do we get a boss here?
This is definitely a...
Oh wait, it should be here, no?
Wait a minute.
Maybe there's no boss.
Oh, that's interesting.
Unless I'm not low enough?
I gotta admit, I don't exactly remember where it was.
Inside the pyramid, but...
Yeah, I don't think there's a boss here, guys.
So the west pyramid has no boss.
Wait, unless I was the wrong...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Nope, there's nothing here.
Oh, but hold on, this actually shoots a bit of a hole in the light and dark theory.
Everything has its counterpart?
Uh...
At this point, multiple counterparts to one thing.
Oh, please.
It's like some twisted version...
of the original one.
But kind of the same one.
It's so weird.
Alright, cool.
Let's keep moving, let's see what else has...
changed.
Oh my god, I can go so fast with the teleport.
Oh...
Wait, what?
Huh?
The fuck is this?
Like, this feels like a bug to me, but apparently it's not, right?
It just feels like some of these places are, like, bugged.
But maybe they're not.
I don't know.
So this is the west version of...
the mines.
Look at that.
There's all kinds of things up there.
Oh, wow.
Percircium, unstable...
Wait, I need teleportation!
There's unstable?
But I can work with that, maybe.
Hmm, let's try it.
Unstable.
What's that?
Ooh!
That wouldn't be too bad!
You know what, I'm taking that.
I like having the vision.
Oh, this is gonna be insane!
Because I can immediately spot...
Wands and upgrades and hearts and all that.
Look at that!
And then I just dig in!
Dig in, boys!
What's that?
Empty potion.
It's like having wall hack.
It's fantastic!
What's that?
A torch!
Sure.
Okay.
Some arrows.
This is not the neuter I know.
This is so weird.
All of this is just...
a head rush.
So I wonder if I can go through the portals here.
I'm gonna assume no.
Wait, what?
Look at this!
Teleportation...
So here's the thing.
The reason I'm picking up the unstable teleportation, by the way...
is that, remember in the...
snowy depths...
there was this eye.
And I could totally fill it with a liquid.
And look, there's teleportation in here.
So I think I need teleportation for that, but I don't know about unstable, but that's all I have.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Tell me we get perks here, too.
Uh...
Okay, so we're at the left side right now.
Oh!
I'm sorry!
Yeah, look at this!
Oh my god!
It just keeps going, guys!
What's that?
Ooh, nah, I don't want that.
Facing.
Gases near you ignite automatically?
I don't know if I like any of these.
But maybe this is the time to explore.
Sixty health.
That's like, useless for me.
Maybe that one would be cool.
I'm immune to fire, right?
Yeah, sure.
Let's take it.
And now, what do we got?
Look how cheap these are!
Yar!
So cheap, yar!
See...
I mean, I'm just gonna leave them here.
I can always come back for this?
I don't really want any of these, I don't think.
I already have a bunch of crap.
No, actually, there's something I wanna do.
I wanna do...
Shit, did I leave behind...
I had an alpha, didn't I?
Fuck.
I wanted to use it on that.
Dang it.
What's this?
Every modifier-type spell in the current wand is applied to a projectile.
But...
What?
How is this even good?
Because every modifier-type spell in a wand...
is already being applied to a projectile.
That's the whole point of a modifier spell.
Maybe just to have two of them.
If you wanna replicate it.
But why not just use a double spell for that?
Okay, whatever.
Weird.
That's weird.
Gold for me.
Dude, I wanna go into...
Oh, dude, we're going into the fungal caverns.
If there even is one here.
And then we gotta try the pahasilma.
Dude!
That's gotta be what it means.
Remember in there?
There were three eyes, right?
Eyes layered on top of each other?
It probably means I need to go to three of those locations.
West.
Middle.
East!
Right?
Who's shooting me?
Alright, die.
Show me the world.
That guy had a wand.
Oh, they're my friends.
Alright, come on, gang.
I have a whole raiding party right now.
Let's move!
Ah, shit, I'm stuck.
Bro, I'm not afraid of the fungal caverns.
I've been to worse fungal places, trust me.
This is nothing to me.
Nothing.
Uh-oh.
There's quite a lot of these small assholes.
That was actually kind of annoying.
I need ad mana, damn it!
Oh, what's that?
It's phloemoxium.
Freeze charge.
Acid trail.
No, I don't like any of that.
No, thanks.
Oh, nice.
Get some health.
That guy's also healing somehow.
Where are you?
What's that?
Soil pouch.
Some soil going.
Let's see if we can't get high here.
For some reason, I haven't been able to get high.
You've got to find a big concentration of mushrooms, though.
Okay, don't want that.
Oh, nice.
More HP.
What do we have?
Nothing good?
I feel like I should start appreciating the ad mana more whenever I find it.
It seems so rare right now.
When you need it, you know, you can't find it.
But I found quite a lot in the past.
Just not this time around, it seems.
A hoodlum.
Destroy the acid.
I mean, I'm immune to these guys, but they're just annoying.
I really need another spell to deal with these guys.
And now that I'm explosion immune, I should maybe consider making some kind of big boom.
Big bada boom.
On a wand.
You know, just to clear the area.
Of small annoyances.
I think it's smart.
It's the smart thing to do.
Rocks?
Eh?
Yes.
We're doing the rocks.
But for that to work, I need to grab the alpha that I left somewhere.
And the question is, where is that?
Wait, where's the...
Where's the...
Where's the book?
And where's the pyramid?
Maybe that's not here.
Maybe that's a change?
Oh, hold on.
Oh, bomb surprise.
Wow.
Auto aim.
Oh, that's actually really good.
But I need add mana.
No, I'm not taking that.
Nope.
Nope, nope, nope.
Oh, there's a chest there.
Wow.
I'm finding so much.
It feels naughty, guys.
It feels like I'm not supposed to have all this that I have.
I have too much.
I'm too strong.
Oh, you've got some mushrooms here.
What's that?
Acceleration?
That's the bottom.
What is that?
Berserkium.
You know what?
I will eat some.
Eat some Berserkium, then we throw this away.
Grab that.
Refresh it.
Straight up.
Uh-oh.
That's pheromone.
I don't even care about pheromone anymore, now that I have so much healing.
Although, you know what?
I kind of want to experiment with pheromone on more enemies.
Because if I never tried it on that guy, right?
I never would have discovered that stuff.
So, maybe there's other enemies that have special effects when you pheromone them.
Okay, so there's a portal here.
I'm not taking that.
What am I even doing here?
Oh, yeah.
I'm looking for add mana.
Oh!
Yo!
There's a little shop.
Triple spell.
I have bloodlust.
I wonder if that's worth using now.
I mean, okay.
So, the reason I'm scared of this is because of those teleporter guys.
But it would... I guess it depends on how much damage I do and how quickly, right?
Because I could instantly kill myself if I'm not careful.
Yeah, I'm not going to risk it.
Not right now.
Maybe I should take...
Get rid of that one.
Take that one.
Just have another one.
I love those things.
They're so cool.
What's up, fools?
The sad thing is, when you do a black hole, it consumes the gold.
That is like a very sad thing.
Okay, not what I need.
This is crazy.
I give zero fucks.
I just run right through.
Also, look at how much HP I'm losing.
Like, toxic shit is definitely... Ooh, more rocks.
Sure.
Maybe I won't take rocks anyway.
Depends what I'll find, right?
But it would be nice to have like a homing rock.
Okay, do we have one of those shops over here?
Or is that even the right level I'm in?
I think it is this level.
Maybe not.
Maybe it's on the other side.
That was a bit risky of me.
What if there was electricity in here?
That would have been really bad for me.
I mean, you can sort of scout with the black hole.
This is the most ultimate way of digging.
There's just nothing that comes close.
Spiral arc.
Toxic mist.
Cloud of toxic mist.
What if I put homing on that?
You know what?
We're gonna try it.
Wait, what was that?
Oh!
That must be a worm.
Or did I just break something?
I must have broke something.
In fact, let me go up there right now.
Wow, I actually broke this whole shop.
Do I have homing?
Maybe I don't even have it.
Welp.
I'll put this here, I guess.
This can be a storage wand of sorts.
Because I can just... Why not just do this?
Right?
Hold on, let me see what that changes.
Yeah, that's pretty cool, I guess.
It's not always got a teleport, though.
It's a little icky.
You know it is what it is.
Maybe I'll just do this.
There.
Now.
Now it will always do it.
Oh, wait, a shuffle!
Oh, shit.
That's the issue.
This one casts nine spells per cast.
What was it that I wanted to do with so many... I had an idea for that.
If I could cast a lot of...
Oh, those were the barriers that I had, but I don't have them anymore.
Ah, well.
This is fine as well.
I like it.
No, I don't like it, actually.
I'll take it back.
But if I put modifiers and stuff, that should be okay.
As long as there's no projectiles.
That way we can add a little more space up here.
Do I really want this?
I don't want this.
We can even put...
Hey, this is actually kind of neat.
This will give you protection while I teleport, I guess.
Right?
I guess so.
But it is shuffle, so we have to remember that.
Okay.
Cool.
Let's just see how that works in practice.
Okay, that is... that is...
Okay, no, no, no.
That's weird.
We gotta get rid of the quadruple.
I think that's messing things up.
Why is it... wait, why is it doing that?
Wait, am I deflecting myself with that?
I think that's what's happening.
Yeah, that's... that's cool.
All right.
We got a couple more slots...
to play with.
I really need Tinka with wands everywhere.
Maybe I should just go through right now and look for that.
Maybe there's a chance I get it, right?
Oh, will you stop it?
Little asshole.
Okay, so now I'm here.
Uh-oh.
Oh, there it is.
Oh, they're so mad.
Show me the goods.
Oh, is that what I think it is?
Guys, I'm immune to everything.
Holy shit.
Nothing can fucking kill me now.
Well, except for Polymorph.
Now we have eliminated everything but Polymorph as a danger here.
That's fantastic.
I have no fear of water anymore.
Maybe I should just run around and holding an Ukuskivi at this point.
Just have it in my head.
Look at this, always casts electricity.
Amazing.
Ow!
Dude, this game is way too fun.
I don't understand how it's so entertaining still.
Diggity-dig.
Dig down.
Oh, hello.
You want to try and kill me?
Good luck, bitch.
You're gonna kill yourself.
Uh, you're nothing.
I am a god.
I cannot be stopped.
Teleport bolt.
Don't even care about it.
This
is pure chaos.
Pure chaos.
I'm going straight through, guys.
West Heezy Base.
Oh, man.
Now where's the entrance to my... to my perks?
Show me the perks.
Maybe I passed it already.
Oh, no, here it is.
Wow.
That was a perfect shot.
Incredible.
What's that?
Recoil?
Water to something?
What's that?
Ground to sand?
Wait, really?
That sounds insane.
Summon Tiny Ghost?
Say what?
Is
that...
We have become complete.
This is it.
Holy shit.
Oh, nothing can stop us now.
What am I taking here, though?
That one.
Why not?
I'm gonna try...
That one...
No, wait, I don't have any space.
Well, I have something stuck in my teeth.
Uh, ping pong pattern.
Why am I keeping this?
I'll keep it.
For now.
So here's what I'm gonna do.
Now that I can switch things out everywhere, I will actually have a transport wand.
I'm just gonna fill it.
We can always switch it up on the fly.
This is so awesome.
Just put all the shit in here.
Maybe not all of it.
Uh, this one stays there.
Something like that, you know?
Like there.
Bunch of shit.
Wonder what happens if I shoot it.
This one seems cool.
What does this do?
Makes any hard, solid materials within a projectile's range turn into sand.
Oh, wait, I tried this once before, I think.
It's kinda nuts.
Also, I can make this infinite.
With the right setup here.
Oops.
There's a fly in my face.
Fucking summer.
That's why, that's what happens when you have the windows open.
They come in here, and they mess with you.
Uh...
Yeah.
This is cool.
I'm a little overwhelmed because it's going so well.
What's this?
Summons a tiny ethereal being to your health.
It may cast stronger spells depending on how much damage you have suffered.
Really?
Wait, how does that work?
Oh, I can only have one?
Oh, that's weird.
I don't know if I like that.
Well, that depends how good it is.
You know, maybe it's super dope.
Who knows?
I'll take that.
I'm gonna make this all the colors of the rainbow.
That seems like a good idea.
What's that?
Transmute drops of acids from nothing.
That's like the only thing I'm not immune to.
At this point.
Could be cool though.
I'll take that one too.
Because they're so cheap.
I have 40,000 gold!
Damn!
Hey!
That's nice.
That's really...
I'll take that too.
And look, I can just go like that and I'm back.
God, tinker with wands everywhere is just...
Unbelievably good.
If I had the choice between this wand right here, at the start of a run, or tinker with wands, I would have a hard time deciding.
That's how good it is.
There's something in my teeth.
It's annoying me.
Yeah, I don't care about electricity.
But maybe I can still get stunned.
That's something I gotta keep in mind.
What are you doing, sir?
Boomerang!
See, that is the ideal spell to use with a healing bolt.
Let me quickly test it.
Yeah, look, it goes straight back into...
Look, it's actually insane.
Sir, will you give my wand back please?
You don't know how to handle that, trust me.
You are not a certified teleporter.
You have not gained the appropriate license for that.
Only I can do that.
Blackel.
I kinda wanna try to go to ancient laboratory.
I wonder if there's another boss there.
I literally don't care about any damage.
It's wild.
Yeah, you better look the other way.
The gods have answered my prayers.
Critical hit plus.
Wait, can you stack this?
I wonder.
I mean,
I'm tempted to take the critical hit.
But...
We're doing this for science now.
Two excretes!
Fuck yeah, it works!
Get that one.
What else?
Maybe even...
Oh, I don't know.
This one, I guess.
I take no electricity damage, I take no explosion, we can do some crazy shit, right?
And watch this now.
You know what, guys, I gotta go brush my teeth real quick.
I have something in my tooth.
I can't stand it.
I'll be right back.
I had to floss it out.
That was indeed a little piece of something.
I got it out!
The tooth is cleansed again.
We're back in business.
Okay, so...
Let's see here, we have an ad mana.
We can do some shit with that for sure.
Let me see my setup here.
I guess I could...
I mean, I guess I just added...
But can I double dip with it?
That's the question here.
Now it's super slow.
Wait, why is that suddenly...
Oh, it adds castelay.
Oh, interesting.
But then we needed the...
Where is it?
This one.
We're running out of space here.
Maybe I'll disregard the light.
Okay.
Full mana for sure.
So this... Oh, this removes point 13.
This adds point 17.
So if I add another...
Let's just remove that for now, just as a test.
Oh!
Whoa!
Wow!
Look at the damage!
I thought it was 300!
It's 3000!
Yo!
Wait...
What about this?
Oh.
Yeah, that's too much.
That's a bit too much.
Oh, man.
Hold on.
I gotta be able to do this in another way.
This costs 12 mana.
Oh, wait.
We're just gonna do this?
Not quite.
Wait.
Reduces castelay by point 17.
Exactly the same amount as this.
So wait, why is this not...
I guess we must have a little bit extra castelay.
There's a tiny amount of castelay.
If we can get rid of that somehow.
This one adds castelay.
This one does too.
Okay, hold on.
Put this back in, because this was nice.
This was super good.
Where is it?
There.
So that's... Wait, why do I not do any damage now?
Wait.
Did I destroy the statue completely or what?
Is it broken?
Oh yeah, it is broken.
Okay.
So that is a lot of damage.
If I remove this...
It's pretty much the same.
Maybe it's a little bit...
It is better.
But now... Oh, wait.
We don't have mana for that.
That would be too much.
My question, if I could do this now...
I'll be double dipping on something here.
Let's say I do that, right?
Look, the damage doesn't display anymore.
The hell, man?
Because if we're double dipping, we're not.
Okay.
So this one does a quadruple...
Scatter spell.
When did the double dip work?
I forgot how that worked.
Was it like that?
We could quadruple into an extra...
Like, one, two, three, and then this one...
Wait, wait, wait.
Well, that's chaotic as fuck.
Shit, I don't remember.
I just do that now.
Oh, it's because of that.
I mean, this seems insane, doesn't it?
It really does.
It doesn't get much better than that.
Do run out of mana with that, though.
Same amount.
What if I were to do this?
Same thing.
Okay.
I mean, I'm not going to complain.
This is already a crazy upgrade.
It's actually insanity.
Now, I want to make a wand that also...
Oh, wait, do we need... I kind of want to put speed on this one, too.
But I guess there's no more room.
I could remove that.
What if, instead of that, I add another damage or bloodlust?
Oh, that's maybe a bit too scary, isn't it?
That's too scary for me.
If we do this, though...
Let's see here now.
Oh, we can't see the damage anyway.
But that should definitely...
...do enough, right?
It's either... So the question for me right now is either a damage plus, or replace it with an extra chainsaw.
Or replace the spark bolt with this one, which is, I guess, better.
But then we need an extra mana, add mana, and I don't have that.
I'm just going to leave it like this for now.
This seems good.
Yeah.
We can experiment with that.
The cool thing is we can experiment it on the fly.
We don't need to be at base.
This is such an amazing thing.
Actually, hold on.
This does drain 5 mana.
This also drains 5 mana, so if I get rid of that...
...and do this...
Hey!
I think I may prefer that.
I think I like that more.
This costs 10 mana.
I do like having an extra layer of shield on me.
That's nice.
Then we have the teleport.
This is all modifiers.
Perfect.
And that should be okay.
We don't need to do this down here anymore.
Let's leave this here.
And let's leave this here.
That one, we can stay, I guess.
I don't know why I'm carrying around this Nala.
It just seems so rare.
Hold on.
It does reduce castelay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold up a second.
Dummy spell.
We need a dummy spell.
If we do... if we do this... on that...
Oh wait, but we still need to do...
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Hold on, I have an idea.
I lost my train of thought.
Fuck!
What was I just about to do?
I removed that.
I was gonna use that on that.
So I removed castelay.
Like that.
It doesn't seem to...
So this one was 0.13.
That's 0.26 in total.
That's 0.25.
That can't be the decider here.
There's no way.
What if I just add this?
Nah.
Alright, fine.
Let's just rock with that.
I guess I can also switch colors on the fly if I want to be red or blue.
Let's be blue.
I like blue.
Blue is cool.
When I get tired of it, we'll switch it up.
Okay.
That's cool, man.
Let's keep going.
Boink.
Also, I'm rocking the energy run.
Yeah.
Jesus.
The damage.
Oh man, instant kill the spider.
Portal there.
There's actually a wand up there.
Look at this.
Insta-dead.
Oh, we got a yellow color now.
You know what?
I like yellow.
Fuck the blue.
Yes, that looks cool.
Very cool.
Let's see what we got here.
Feared by worms.
Fungal disease.
A mournful spirit.
Dying creatures leave behind a spirit that deals damage in a small area.
I don't like any of these.
I am rerolling.
Unlimited spells.
Oh, you can see everywhere.
That may actually be useful here.
Guys, this one.
All seeing eye.
I think I want it.
Fuck yeah.
And...
All right.
That seems good.
Let's go.
Now we see everything.
And we've explored most of the stuff anyway in these areas here.
So I don't need to know where I haven't been.
You know what I mean?
Oh man, being able to spam this right now is just so amazing.
Feels good.
Blow everything up.
Hold on, actually.
I feel like I'm doing very shitty damage.
Am I doing shitty damage?
Hold on, we gotta test on the statues up here.
These are intact.
What's happening?
Did I fuck up my one?
Oh no, I definitely didn't.
It's still good.
All right.
I just felt like I did very less damage to that guy.
Or very little.
Look at this.
Okay, let's test.
Can I be electrocuted?
Can I get stunned?
No, look at that.
I don't give a shit.
That's awesome.
Okay, no need to be afraid of getting stunned either.
Oh man, oh man.
That is lovely.
Oh, but the next time we gotta re-roll, that's gotta be 40,000 something gold.
But now we're getting so much more gold because of double greed.
Oh man, the game is struggling to handle the power of my wand.
At least I think it's my wand.
Holy shit.
Gunpowder trail?
Yo.
What?
That seems awesome.
But not awesome enough.
Oh man, so much gold.
Oops, I got teleported.
This is a complete mess.
So I'm farming gold so I can re-roll.
Oh man, the game is slowing down so much.
Holy crap.
Oh wow.
Phew, this area is really tough on my CPU.
Normally I would be deathly afraid of what's happening on my screen here, but I'm not.
In fact, I don't give a fuck.
Keep going.
Hold on, we gotta find...
Where the perks at?
Oh shit, huh?
I got teleported so far for some reason.
I can definitely feel the lack of having speed on this.
The lack of speed is really bad.
Come on, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down.
Oh, here it is.
Didn't mean to pick those up actually, I was looking over here.
Circle of transmogrification.
Fuck!
I didn't mean to buy it, I misclicked.
I was gonna go right, I was pressing D, but I accidentally hit the wrong button, E.
Shit.
It's nice to have, I guess.
Yo, that would be invisibility?
I think I want invisibility.
I'm taking it.
Hmm, do I want to buy anything here?
Maybe I'll buy another one of these.
Yeah, let's do it.
I'm gonna get so much money anyway.
Oh!
Did you see that guy?
He was pink, that could have been a teleport, no, a polymorph guy.
You know, that's the nice thing about having vision everywhere, you can see things coming.
I never considered that, I always thought, oh, it's for finding secrets and shit, right?
But that is another use.
See danger coming around the corner.
And shooting people long range.
Damn.
This dude is taking so little damage.
Cool.
Just keep going.
Oh man, the game is slowing down so much.
Oh wait, I'm still taking damage from that attack he does, so it's not melee damage.
It's something else.
What's that?
Null shot.
Increases a projectile's duration dramatically but removes all damage.
Oh, yo!
Hello!
That's actually really nice.
Watch this.
We're gonna throw that on there.
And...
Oh, you're gonna stay there?
That's perfect.
I feel like I need more...
slots here.
Hmm...
I guess I'll just throw it on this one.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
Actually, take this and throw it up here.
I don't know.
Throw that one away.
Or put it down on the other wand.
Shit.
Also, can you stop shooting?
I gotta think.
This one gets replaced.
There.
And then on this one...
We're just gonna do this.
Okay, that still works decently.
And then this guy...
is shuffled but that's maybe okay.
I don't know how that's gonna work.
We'll have to see.
Let me put mega speed on it.
Holy fuck.
I mean...
You know what?
If anything, we should probably...
put a quadruple.
Oh, we don't have that.
We do have that.
So we're gonna put...
How's this gonna work?
The shuffle is gonna ruin it.
So we need to find a non-shuffle wand, basically.
Let's see how this does.
Oh, fuck.
We're at this spot again.
Is there really...
no perks here?
Shit.
Okay.
I am actually tempted to just...
Yeah, I'm gonna go through here.
I'm going through.
And now we're in the center, look.
Let's see here.
There's gotta be a wand here.
That isn't shuffle.
Shuffle...
also shuffle.
No shuffle.
Let's just take that for now.
And on this guy, we're gonna put...
all of this stuff.
We don't need that one.
That should be crazy.
Right?
Let's see.
Maybe remove that.
Because the acceleration is actually making it look weird.
Like, it starts being a smooth cut.
And then it goes like...
You know, it's like the game can't keep up, basically.
So if I now put that...
Oops, put that there.
Let's try it.
That feels better to me already.
That feels better.
Yeah.
That's cool.
Okay.
And then...
This is a shuffle wand.
I gotta replace that now.
With this guy.
Let me do that.
Alright.
Very cool.
Are there any spells I would like to have here?
Giant Firebolt.
Oh.
Actually.
Remove bounce?
Let me think.
Remove bounce.
No, I think I would like that.
Bounce is okay.
That is that weird thing.
Actually, this wand is kind of nuts.
0.50.
Oh, it shoots two spells per cast.
What else do we have over here?
The homing!
I'll take that and keep it.
And I gotta keep an eye out for...
my alpha spell that I put somewhere.
I have no idea where I put it.
Chances are I put it near one of the holy mountains.
So let's actually go explore.
Wait, what?
Wait, what's happening?
The fuck was that?
Ow!
I got a jar in my face.
Oh, hold up a second.
What's this now?
So right now we're in the center of the world, right?
Let's keep exploring here.
Let's just see what we find.
Oh, this is much smoother.
Look at the cut here.
It's super smooth.
I much prefer this to what I had before.
Oh, this is satisfying as hell.
I am perfecting my black hole wand.
So I can't tell if I've been here or not because everything is visible now.
So that guy is, like, purplish.
I... I'm not sure what he does.
I'm not sure what he does.
It would be nice to actually have that remove recoil spell right now.
I'm getting a little too much recoil on my wand.
Oh!
What if I just dig down?
What if I disregard?
I don't give a fuck.
Yeah!
Oh!
Fuck, that was close.
Oh, that was scary.
Yikes!
All right.
All right, man.
What's this?
Fireballs.
All right.
Holy crap.
Now that guy...
What do you do again?
Show me.
Oh, it bounces off every time.
Actually kind of annoying when I try to test these enemies.
You up there.
Hahaha, this is so much fun.
I just shoot a hole wherever the fuck I want and then the enemies get shot down with my machine gun after.
Like, brrr!
Hey!
Brrr!
And they're just dead.
What's up, dudes?
How's it hanging?
Hey!
Cool.
What's up, my dude?
Hee-hoo!
Bye-bye.
I love the sounds they make when they die.
They go, hee-hoo!
And I'm slowly amassing good wealth as well.
Oh, I checked that wand already.
So the issue here is, I don't know where I've been and where I haven't.
That's the one downside to having this perk here.
But I guess if there's enemies, I haven't been there, so that's an indicator.
And it's a good enough indicator, I would say.
I see you there.
Whoa!
Ah!
Fuck, I'm stuck!
That was a scary-ass wand!
That's gotta be an earthquake wand!
What is it?
Yeah, that's an earthquake.
Alright, that was kinda cool though.
Man, I love my new black hole wand.
This is so much smoother.
Fantastic.
Oh, hold on a second!
Oh, wait a minute!
Is this only affecting the- wait, is it?
Hold on.
Okay.
Oh, it's the same amount.
So maybe it only works on the black- wait, increases the projectile's duration dramatically.
It removes all damage and explosion from it.
Okay.
Just to be safe, I think I may want to do this so I can apply these two things.
And not that I need speed on Circle of Wigger, but... you know?
Like, put it... here.
Wait, how does that work?
I can't tell whether or not this thing is living longer or not.
I guess it is.
I'm just gonna assume it is.
Okay.
Hey, fool!
What do you do?
Look at his head!
They're actually very distinct.
We got an uku?
Uku dead.
What's that?
Hamis.
I should have petted it.
Ah, fuck this guy.
So annoying.
You know what?
The way to deal with those guys, the teleporters?
Circle of Transmogrification, baby.
Right?
Or you freeze them?
Basically, you make them unable to act.
Wait, why did that black hole come back?
So wait, what is this place?
The wizards, then?
I kind of forgot what it said.
Oh, he's... oh no.
He's buffing them.
Oh my god, this wand is the best wand I've ever made.
It just shreds.
Okay.
Kill that dude.
Whoa.
Hey.
Calm down, people.
Oh, he's shooting black holes.
Oh, that's actually so cool.
I couldn't hit him because my projectiles got sucked into the black hole.
Very cool.
Fuck you, man.
So the way those guys work is the very first instance of damage they take is when we switch positions.
So you need something hot and heavy to deal with them.
Hold on, my ear is itchy.
There's all kinds of things wrong with my body today.
I got things stuck in my teeth.
My ears are itchy.
Man, I should really be picking up this gold.
Yeah.
I'm just completely obliterating the layout of the levels as well.
The more I play, the more everything gets destroyed.
You know what's crazy about this?
My wand is not even that complicated.
It's actually a simple enough wand.
It's just a trigger with a bunch of chainsaws on it.
And yeah, I add a bit of damage, but that's essentially just what that is.
And it's like doing this amount of damage at this time in the game.
Kind of blows my mind a little bit.
God, I need to find a water bottle or something.
Let's drink some of this.
Where am I even going?
I have no clue.
Oh, you there.
Stop puffing.
Oh, hey, guys.
Absolutely crazy.
Oh, my God, there's mages everywhere.
Holy shit, that was scary.
Oh, wow.
A heart.
Fuck yeah.
This is indeed the wizards then.
Look how many wizards there are.
It's where they all hang out.
Wait, is he shooting pheromone bolts?
He has a wand.
Stop having wands.
Critical plus?
Um, formation trifurcated.
Maybe I want the critical plus.
Just to have...
Uh-oh.
Switch it back.
I wish my primary wand had more slots.
Wait, is my black hole attracting his black hole?
Oh, man.
That looked awesome.
Did you see that?
Oh, more health.
I don't even know what my goal... I'm just having fun killing things right now.
I don't even fucking care what's going on.
I think the next step, by the way, is to...
Whoa!
The hell?
Now that I have teleport wands, it's time to check out the music riddle.
Because we can move fast now.
But I also kind of want to go to the meat realm.
I forgot exactly where it was.
So...
Let me quickly take a break, because I need to fix the audio thing with the map.
Because I was going to go on the map now, but I remembered that I had this issue with the audio.
So let me find a compromise.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
So, let me know if this sounds okay.
I'm going over here.
Just tell me if the music sounds weird.
And give it a bit of time.
Because the audio is technically being doubled.
Because it's going through a media source, and also it's being output through the...
main audio speaker, so...
it's twice.
So maybe there was like a little delay between them and it would sound weird.
But if it's okay...
then we're good to go.
Okay.
Let me see.
It sounds okay?
Alright.
Well.
In that case...
Let me also move this over here.
Okay, so here's the thing.
Meat Realm...
Whoops.
It's somewhere here.
Which is very close to the top, actually.
And right now...
I am...
I think...
somewhere here.
Because I was in the art, and I went right.
And I appeared...
in the wizard's den.
Or at least it looks like the wizard's den.
So I think I just gotta go up and see what happens.
That's the plan right now.
And there we go.
I'm just gonna kill these guys real quick.
Oh no!
Oh my god, please!
Die!
Oh, he's immune now.
That's not good.
Alright, that works.
Okay, let's go up.
I do wonder if there's such a thing as lava immunity.
Like being able to swim in lava sounds insane.
Bro, these guys just keep coming!
Who's shooting?
It's you.
Oh no, not this guy again.
It's so confusing when you were being teleported like that.
Money.
We just keep going up now.
And kill things on the way.
Holy shit.
49k money already!
Holy crap!
That's actually wild.
Okay.
Wait.
I've been here.
Why is there a...
Oh, I must have made that hole just now without knowing, probably.
I shot... I must have shot a black hole up there without realizing.
Yeah, yeah.
Now we go straight up.
Oh, we hit some water?
Wait, what?
Entered water!
Yeah, no shit.
What?
What do you mean?
Yeah, we entered water.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, come on.
Wait, this region is called water?
What the hell do you mean?
It's literally just a reservoir of water.
Oh no, there's... Oh, actually...
Oh...
Whenever there's cursed rock, you know something's gonna be good, right?
Or maybe not, I don't know.
Fuck.
Power plant?
I have no idea where I am!
Huh?
What the fuck?
These are new enemies!
Complete the new enemies!
Yo!
What?
Whoa, they have a lot of HP.
Or I do very little damage.
Look at this stuff.
Also, they're healing, it seems.
And they're blocking some of my damage.
What are you shooting?
Some kind of thing.
I'm not sure what that is.
But it scares me.
Oh, I do very little damage to these guys.
What the hell?
Jesus.
I do nothing!
Good thing I'm fire immune, huh?
They're actually healing.
Power plant.
Rotate towards foes.
Damn.
These guys look cool as hell!
So much sand.
I just keep finding new areas!
How is it possible?
How is this game so big?
What's this?
Oh, random damage.
I don't like that.
I tried it once.
It was, like, decent.
But nothing amazing, you know?
I do wonder what it is these guys are shooting at me.
I seem to block it, whatever it is.
I mean, it's whatever, right?
It's probably something.
Something bad if I don't have the perks I have.
But they're also blocking my attacks.
Not all of them, though.
You know what I think?
I think they are blocking all of my chainsaws.
Because look at the damage output I'm doing.
It's, like, in the hundreds.
And there's only two types of damage that I currently have, right?
It's the spark bolt and it's the chainsaw.
Wow, the recoil I have on this is wild.
Gracias.
Man, where am I?
Where are all the fire?
Imagine not having fire resistance here.
You just can't be here.
It's over.
What is that?
It's, like, a mini Colmi Silma.
Oh, a skull is left behind.
And then the shell came out.
Cool.
I'm just gonna...
Let me go around the outline of this place.
I need to figure out exactly what the layout looks like.
Drilling shot.
Oh, whoa!
Hello!
Yo, this wand is nuts.
The only thing is, it has a high recharge time.
And very few...
slots.
That's the bad part.
I was looking for a replacement for my current main wand.
Also, I have a target on me right now.
Can I see what that means?
Maybe it just has higher aim.
More precision or something.
Oh, I definitely need some different damage against these guys.
I have a feeling, electricity will do wonders against these.
Given that they are made of metal and all that.
Okay, so...
Let me get to the western edge here.
So, I came from here.
Let's go down.
Let's see how far down this goes.
I don't know how much recoil I have.
And it's because I'm slippery too, makes it even worse.
That's a heart.
Okay, man, it goes deep.
Power plants.
Look at that guy!
These are all new enemies.
Oh!
Overgrown?
Hold on, I want to kill this dude up here, I saw.
You there.
Oh, he has a shield too.
This place is nuts.
It's fucking crazy.
What is going on?
Holy fuck!
Give me all that money now.
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
And now we're here.
Or are we?
It's like...
Huh.
Let's get high.
Can we finally get high?
Fuck, I'm trying to get high here.
I'm so slow.
I'm definitely tripping balls.
Nothing's happening though.
Okay, so we have this area underneath.
Overgrown caverns.
Have I been here?
In this exact spot?
I think I have.
Look, this one is empty.
Okay, I'm not sure.
Maybe not.
It's hard to say.
I feel like I would have seen this if I was here last time.
This must be maybe a different overgrown cavern.
This is...
This world is massive.
Oh, wait, someone's buffing.
It's you.
You're the one buffing.
I need some other kind of damage here.
Call me crazy, but I feel like I've seen this one before.
So maybe I have been here.
I don't think so.
Yo!
Double scatter spell and concentrated explosion.
I don't know about that.
I kind of like my explosions to be big.
Yo!
A million things.
And again, this place right here?
Just right off the bat.
A million wands.
This is the place you guys call the Wand Mart.
I fucking love that.
At least it looks a lot like that same place.
Okay, so this is now...
Okay, now we're feeling the effects of the Highness.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, we're feeling it.
Oh, it is bad.
Oh, it's kicking in.
Oh, fuck.
Wow, what's that?
Concentrated mana.
I don't even know where I'm going, guys.
I am just flailing in the world.
Drink a bit of that.
Oh, yeah.
Damn.
What is that?
Is that a chest?
No, I'm too high.
It's just a piece of rock.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my screen is fucked.
I want to keep going up.
Okay, this is how I'm going to anchor things in my mind.
I'm going to go up until I hit the surface.
So I can see exactly where on the map this shit is located.
Like, where underneath, you know?
I think that's a decent plan.
Get the money.
Kill that guy.
And then we got to do the music stuff.
In fact, that's got to be the next thing.
Yeah, let's go to the surface and we try the music thingies.
This one sucks.
Wait, where's the power plant now?
Is it up here?
It was.
Okay, so now we just go up.
I want to see exactly where this is located.
Thank you.
Let me drink some berserkium.
Because these guys take a lot of shots.
It actually helps a lot.
74,000 gold.
What's that?
Nothing interesting.
I think they're immune to melee damage.
If I would have kicked them, what then?
Okay, nothing's happening.
Not working.
Oh, okay.
Look at this now.
Sand caves.
Very cool.
Finally doing some damage again here.
Keep going up, keep going up.
Dude, I have never been more in the gamer zone than right now.
I'm actually in some kind of trance.
You know when you're in a flow state?
That's what I am in right now.
My brain has been tuned to Noita.
The Noita frequency 666.
Wait, are they invisible?
What's going on?
Why are they faded like that?
What the hell is this now?
Another overgrown cavern.
I mean, sure.
Whatever.
Very confusing.
And a wand.
Wow.
I will say no to that.
Little ants.
This is the place I've been to.
It's gotta be.
Oh yeah, now we're back with these things.
That keep spawning.
Yeah, I feel like I've seen this wand before.
What's that?
Concentrated light bounce.
Makes a projectile release a bundle of concentrated light as it bounces?
Oh.
That's pretty cool, I guess.
Alright.
Not my cup of tea right now, though.
I need some stronger stuff.
Whew.
Well, well, well.
I shall be taking some of these goodies.
Oil trail?
You know what?
I will not take it.
I will take fireball orbit, though.
Chain... causes a projectile to cast a copy of itself upon expiring.
Ooh.
I think I like it.
Anything else I would like here?
Don't think so.
Seems like crazy wand, though.
Lot of slots on it.
Wait, guys, will you stop this?
Wait, why are they... is there ambrosia here?
Also need to replace this wand again.
There we go.
Nah, fuck off.
I don't want to deal with you.
Yeah, see, look at the explosion over here.
I've been here.
For sure I've been here.
Yeah, look at us.
Okay, so we're actually sort of back where we have been before.
That's kind of reassuring.
The rainbow.
I feel like that's superior to all the other colors.
Let's do that.
I like rainbow.
And that is freeze charge.
I think maybe I want it.
Here's a projectile of frozen charge that it will release on impact.
Add five ice damage.
Oh, this one also reduces cast delay.
I didn't even notice.
What if we tried to just do this?
Is that too crazy?
I don't know.
I think maybe I just want speed on it.
Although I do like having this.
It's like more safety, right?
It's not like I'm lacking damage.
Not really.
I got another heart.
That's insane.
Damn.
A lot of energy spheres.
Okay.
What do we got here?
I've seen this one before.
The fuck is that?
Mystery?
Oh, eat it.
Quick, eat it.
Eat the mystery.
All right, that's better.
Now we're back in our normal state of mind.
Oh, yeah.
See, now we're talking.
This is the sort of thing I kind of want.
But it is limited.
All right, so now we've made it to here.
And what is up here then?
Ah, this stuff.
Okay, don't go too far left or right.
We're going straight up.
Based on everything, we should be in the desert, right?
Oh, we're right here.
No fucking way.
Holy fuck.
So that means...
overgrown cavern here.
It's like interspersed with...
interspersed with...
power plant stuff.
Right?
In a weird way.
Also, I'm confusing myself now, actually.
We need to exactly map this.
This is not perfect.
So it's all right below this watchtower.
Wait, what's that sound?
Maybe that's just the sound we play here.
Okay, so let's go try the music stuff.
One in the pond.
One on the ledge.
One under the sun.
And...
one somewhere.
But if I just start from one side and go to the other, it should be okay.
I think the one we saw just there is the...
yeah.
So this is the first one.
We're going to try and time this.
Wait.
Go!
Where's the next?
May have been quicker to just black hole my way through this, but whatever.
Wait, did I miss one?
Oh wait, I think the next one is in the pond.
Here we go.
Okay, there we go.
It's going.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
I believe the next one is on top of the tree.
So somewhere here, yeah.
Got it.
Go!
And then we have one in the snow somewhere.
There's no way the first one stopped playing.
Yet.
Shit, shit, shit.
I don't remember exactly where it is.
I could have checked my map, I guess.
But it should be here somewhere.
Okay.
Shit.
Ah!
There we go.
Oh, actually.
Oh yeah, right.
So now I'm playing all of them.
Wait a minute, where did I find that note?
With the... Oh, that was inside the pyramid.
We may have to go back to the pyramid, but let me just go up here real quick.
Remind me what's up here.
Right.
Excuse me.
Oh, look at the rainbow.
That looks awesome.
The rainbow shot.
This whole fucking clownscape is getting destroyed.
Wait, why is everything...
Huh?
Wait.
There's like an aura around me that destroys the cloud.
I don't understand what's happening.
Wait, do I have some kind of...
Wait, why is that?
Huh?
Whoa!
What the fuck is going on?
Wow.
We're going.
Wait, is he blackholing me?
Maybe activating the music things actually did something.
I'm going to keep going up.
There's nothing.
This doesn't look too good.
Okay, the background does change.
Something's happening.
Everything becomes gray.
Fuck.
Let me go back down.
Also, I have to remember, I'm actually invisible.
Okay, so obviously, it's not all the way up there.
Oh, the moon is to the right.
You know what?
I kind of want to investigate the moon again.
Whoa.
Bro, look how far I'm falling.
Where's the cloudscape even?
Oh, you know what?
Maybe the background turned different color because it's night now.
It was sort of reddish, right?
As if the sun was going down.
Well.
Let's have a look out here.
There's got to be something in this place.
Hey, speak enough.
It's another music wand.
Whoa.
Oh, two mana max.
That's really bad.
Ocarina.
Wait, Ocarina?
I actually don't know what Ocarina means.
I know there's a game called Ocarina of Time, but...
I didn't know Ocarina was something that actually meant something real.
I guess I will try it.
Wait a minute.
Look at the note.
Speaking of the moon.
Hold on.
I have a picture of this.
I need to confirm something with myself.
It says note F.
Note F.
I thought it was like a D, but it's actually a note F.
That's exactly what that was.
And then it said zero.
Or O, or whatever that is.
Do we have that?
Is that a thing?
Oh, wait a minute.
What is that one?
Wait, is that the same?
Okay.
Fuck.
I'm really lacking slots here.
Let me just put these here for now.
What is it with these fucking notes?
That's actually a sick beat.
Sounds like the start of classic.
Uh...
I forget the name of the band.
Fuck.
Let me see here.
Maybe we spell something with this.
What can we spell with these letters?
So that means G sharp.
The only reason I know that is because there's something called C sharp.
Which is programming related.
I actually don't know anything about music theory.
I do not... I think these are just pitches, right?
That's all that is.
It's like higher pitch, lower pitch.
Music for your ears.
It has a speed as well, isn't that interesting?
What if we put them in alphabetical order here?
A, A2, B, C...
Wait, did I try this once before?
I think I did.
But not with these ones.
E...
F...
G...
Oh wait, I forgot C.
There we go.
Oh, we also forgot the A.
Okay.
Oh, and the B.
Jesus.
Okay.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
There we go.
Oh, I also forgot these, but...
Hmm.
Okay, hold on.
So we know of two places now that have a music wand.
And there are some notes you can pick up.
The logical question is...
Is there a difference in the notes between these two places, or is it the same note selection?
I guess I can just go over there and check if I really want to see.
Although I did kind of mess this up, I should have taken a picture of this before I messed it.
But...
Inside the moon, it definitely had DF and then something zero.
So I think I want to keep this one just for that.
Hold on, let me see the picture again.
It also said...
Dot.
It actually says DF and then my colon.
Circle.
So basically...
It did like...
It's like this.
That's what's at the end.
That's the closest thing I have.
And then underneath, it said something like this.
Dot.
Gamma.
O.
Arrow up.
I could be overthinking this, but...
I'm not sure if this is actually meant to be a Greek letter.
Or if this is actually just a language.
And this one could be A.
And this one could be B, you know?
And this one could be C.
Who knows?
If that is the case, what we need is a cipher.
We need a key.
We need a stone made of Rosetta.
To translate.
So if that is corresponding to a node and it says DF zero...
That could mean...
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe that's like some simple music theory here that I'm not actually understanding.
Maybe this is a simple thing...
That everyone who studies music actually knows about.
But I don't.
I have no fucking clue.
I don't know what that means.
And where am I right now?
So I went up from here.
Right?
So somewhere in the sky up here...
There's some clouds.
And then we have a triangle.
Something like that.
And it also has a sort of platform above it.
Like that.
And then we have music notes.
I'm just going to write that.
I'm not going to type it out.
Music wand.
Plus notes.
Like that.
Weird.
Alright.
Let's leave these here for now.
I'll keep this one up here.
Ocarina node F.
Let's see if the other notes in the world also are called Ocarina.
Or if they're different.
Also my wand is up here.
Do I want to keep this wand though?
It is definitely a better storage wand, isn't it?
So I'm just going to do that.
It's actually a really big wand.
Then put all of this down here now.
Yeah, I can't cast any of this because it has such a low mana.
How much is it?
Mana max 2.
Shit.
There we go.
Just put some back up here like that.
Okay.
Cool.
That one.
Let's see what else there is up here.
And why is all of this...
It's burning.
What is happening?
Oh, is that what it is?
Is it... that's probably what that is actually.
Never mind.
I know what it is.
It's a gas apparently.
Alright.
That's got to be the explanation.
Because it's igniting.
This is actually kind of annoying.
I can't really do anything up here.
I can't stand on any ground.
But I can... I can fly forever with this.
So... not the worst.
Let's see what else we can find up here.
That guy is like impossible to kill.
Jesus.
Did I get you?
I think I did.
Holy shit, this is Uco land.
I mean, I am disintegrating the clouds here.
I'm blowing up their empire and I love it.
It's very satisfying.
What else do we have here?
You know what?
I think I should start doing.
Instead of just going wildly like I'm doing now.
Because so far the game has actually been quite consistent with...
Let's say you find something interesting.
Either something nearby is going to be straight up, right, down or left.
Right?
Think about the store in one of the regions where the hourglass is right above it, right?
Like it's never in some angle.
It's always sort of in nicely predetermined positions, you know?
It's like east, west, north, south.
And now I can't find out where that platform was that I found before.
I think it's somewhere off to the right.
So in general, I think I should just start being more...
Like if I find a place of interest like this.
Let's just try going up from here, you know?
And if nothing, which is most likely the case here, okay.
Then we try to just go right.
I'm just going to keep going like this until something happens.
I'm actually not sure if I'm gaining altitude or not right now.
Am I climbing?
Oh, wait, what?
Something's falling from here?
Ah, okay, here's some stuff.
Oh, what's that?
Hell slime?
I don't like the sound of that.
I'm kidding, I love the sound of that.
Fuck yeah!
Lovely!
Fuck you, dude!
I have come to eradicate your kind.
Take me to your leader.
Oh, I'm taking some damage here.
He says all surprised, as if he never took damage.
Whoa!
At least we have some solid ground to stand on.
Even though it may be hell slime.
Did I just kill that guy with a black hole?
This is a very mysterious place.
Yo, look at that guy.
I literally cannot die.
I am broken.
It's kind of fitting that I'm shooting a rainbow up in the sky, isn't it?
Unfortunately for these guys, there's no pot of gold at the end.
What the fuck?
I'm a worm!
What?
What the hell?
Yo, that was kind of cool.
Okay, I have no idea what's going on in this game anymore.
It has reached that point where it's just... fucking insanity.
Uh oh.
Oh no, we're pulling more...
Ah!
Are we dead?
Is this the end?
Okay, not quite yet.
Let's be careful there.
This seems like a dangerous spot.
I'm gonna move on here.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
Oh, I see now!
I see now, these guys bleed polymorphism!
I understand.
So those guys immediately...
One of the most dangerous things up here.
And when you kill them, do not stand below them.
That's the new rule.
There's another one.
Haha, I don't give a shit about that.
Look at all that polymorphism.
Oh my god!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, that is just terrifying.
Oh no.
This place is nuts.
Go higher.
We're going higher.
What?
The fuck is this?
I can't even read what it says.
Downwards Larpa.
Why are there just spells like this?
Touch of smoke?
Yo, these are expensive.
I mean...
Sure.
Transmutes everything in a short radius into smoke.
Including walls, creatures, and you?
Wait, am I reading that right?
Okay, so that's something you want to shoot with a trigger.
Holy crap.
I feel like I do not want to become smoke.
That almost seems like a death sentence.
Doesn't it?
What is this place?
The music is... weird.
Two.
Oh, there's more.
Rant... oh.
Random spell.
Seda.
Oh, that's another Greek letter.
That ought to be interesting.
Let's get... oh, liquid detonation.
Converse any non-magical leaks into explosive gunpowder.
Put some stuff down here.
I'm actually kind of curious about that.
Copies a random spell in another one.
Oh, no, not that one.
I think I had this one before.
Ugh.
Okay, that's not great.
I've used all my money now.
That was my allowance.
It's ogre.
Wait, these enemies are starting to amass some HP.
We may have to upgrade our wand game here.
Dude, look how much gold I'm getting.
Oh, you know what?
I can easily get that amount of gold back.
It's no problem.
Okay, so this guy bleeds polymorphism.
That is just... the worst.
Is it chaotic as well?
I think it is.
But wait a minute, don't I evaporate liquids?
What does it say?
Oh, gasses.
Shit, okay.
I would pick up... what is that?
Touch of spirits.
What is it?
Are these spells just being here?
Holy bomb.
This is insanity.
Yo, that one is good.
M?
Oh wait, M is...
No, I have that already, never mind, never mind.
Hold on, what is this one?
Nuke Orbits?
No fucking way.
Nuke Orbits.
I kind of want to get it.
That sounds awesome.
I'm getting a very uneasy feeling being here, guys.
This is like the kind of place where it feels like I'm not supposed to be here.
Like, I'm seeing something that is not meant for my eyes.
If that even makes sense.
I'm not ready for this.
Also, what happens when I...
Oh wow, this thing actually cuts through...
Oh, it's just wood.
What the hell is that?
Touch of water?
Touch of spirits?
Oh, spirits as in whiskey.
I thought they were like ghosts spirits.
It's got to be...
whiskey, right?
Look at that.
40k already.
I can buy another spell.
I'm not even losing HP.
This is crazy.
What is that?
Gold to power?
What's that?
Gamma.
Oh, what's that?
Phi?
Yep.
I wonder how many Greek letters they're going to include.
I'm tempted between this one and...
Actually, all three I'm tempted.
I'm going to...
Hold on.
Gold to power.
Spence 5% of your current gold and add damage to a projectile proportional to the amount spent?
Yo!
I feel like that could be insanity later on.
Wow.
All right.
This is really awesome though.
Another nuke orbit.
Oh,
man.
Just like explosions and fire, electricity.
I'm just unfazed.
I don't give a fuck.
Where the hell is this place?
Yo, that's Omega.
That's really good.
I want another one of those.
But I kind of want to check out the other ones too, just to see what they are, you know?
At least I know that the Omega one is really good.
Dude, that's too...
What the fuck is this place?
And you know what actually?
If you notice the layout of this, it looks a lot like the art.
But like a weird fucked up version of it stripped down.
You see all these little pieces here?
This right here is totally the same as the art.
Wait, what is he bleeding?
Oh, teleportation.
That's okay.
Ah, teleportation up here?
I don't give a shit.
I'm teleporting all the time anyway.
Whatever.
What is that one?
A random static projectile spell?
What?
I'm not affected by anything.
Or maybe I was.
I feel like this igniting gasses is actually being really nice here.
Like, this is really helpful.
What is that one?
Ooh, that looks interesting.
Check that out, guys.
Touch of gold.
Touch of gold?
Ooh, I like that.
Hold on, it's just like...
Where's the other one I have?
Touch of smoke.
Wait, transmutes everything in a short radius into smoke.
Is that gonna do the same with gold?
Because that would be insane.
I'm saving for that.
Because if that actually works the way I think it does...
then we're in for a ride here.
What?
Oh, no.
Fucking hell.
Now I lost my bearings.
We gotta find more enemies.
I need gold.
People!
There you are.
Hand over your lunch money.
Daddy needs to go to the store.
I gotta grab a pack of touch of smokes.
Wait, why doesn't that die?
Oh, maybe it is dead.
Whoops.
Guys, this run has been insane.
I wonder how long this has taken so far.
Like, how many hours am I even in?
Look at these, there's new spells here too.
Completely new spells.
What's that?
Inner spell?
Touch of blood.
This is awesome.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Wow, even their projectiles is...
Ooh, man.
These guys are the real baddies.
Holy fuck.
Yeah, let's just get rid of him.
I don't even want to pick up his gold.
That is how afraid I am of that.
Is that a mine?
How is that?
Oh, I guess it's gone now.
Nuke orbit.
Show me the money.
Oops.
I need more big enemies.
That's plasma orbit?
Isn't it?
Hold on.
Yeah, plasma beam orbit.
Oh, yeah.
So much money on these guys.
I'm not going to teleport in there.
That's way too dangerous.
Uh-oh.
I have to remember, when I shoot them, they bleed upwards too.
What do I shoot?
Hey.
Nala.
Mana to damage.
Yo, that one would be crazy because this one is like...
I can make this infinite.
Holy shit.
Dude.
You can make some insane ones with this.
That didn't even occur to me.
Oh, my God.
The potential is out of this world.
Oh, wow.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
What's that?
Naropa explosion.
37K.
Okay, we're going to try that gold one now.
If I can remember where it is.
Oh, that's alpha.
Gamma phi.
No, not gamma.
That's...
What is that one?
It's T.
Tau.
Right, okay.
I don't know what that is.
There's so many of them.
Sigma?
Is that to sum up spells?
Now to find the...
the gold one.
I wonder where that was.
I want to say it was more to the left.
I'm not sure.
Is it over here?
Wait, this is where I entered, I think.
I have no clue where that is.
I think it's close to here.
My God, dude.
You were bleeding a lot of oil.
And that is the inner spell.
A touch of blood.
I think it's close to here.
Is it up or down?
Maybe down.
Uh-oh.
Yeah, just kill that guy.
Get rid of him.
You know what?
The way to prevent being polymorph-ed...
is to have polymorphism turned into something else.
I mean, the chances are astronomically low, but...
that would be the way!
Right?
That is the ultimate way.
Can't really beat that.
Man, where the fuck was this thing?
Meanwhile, I'm collecting more money.
It's actually not the worst.
I
feel like I'm going in circles now.
This is the very bottom, right?
Of this place.
It's an Omega.
Nuke.
Are these clouds being formed again, after I destroy them?
God dang it!
I have no clue.
Seda.
It's a bunch of oil.
Look, it's night now!
What was that one again?
Touch of water.
That's right.
I mean, I didn't go this way because there's all these clouds here, right?
I would have dissolved those if I went that way.
I'm going to be lost here a while, I think.
What is that?
Chaotic Transmutation.
I don't know where to go!
Fuck!
I don't know where I saw it.
I think that one is ripped.
It's ripped.
I feel like it was close to here, if anything.
So, I'm definitely going in circles there.
Let's just try...
Okay, you know what?
One way to be sure about this.
I'm going to go all the way to the west now.
And when I'm all the way to the west...
Oh, wait, this may be it.
This may be the place.
I'm going to systematically go up and down.
That's one way to do it, I guess.
So, all the way to the west first.
Nice.
So, we know it's not here.
Also, what is that?
Spells to power.
Oh...
That sounds interesting, doesn't it?
I'm tempted to just buy it.
But...
Let's just walk around a bit more.
So, it's obviously not up here, because I haven't been here.
There's all these clouds.
So, now we're going to go...
Down.
As much as we can.
Okay.
Let me go a little right.
Let me go up as much as we can now.
Shit, what just fell?
Up, up, up, up.
Okay.
Okay, so there's nothing up here.
Oh, what is that one?
Look at that!
Oh!
What do we got here?
Hold on.
Look at that money.
Blood...
Magic.
What the fuck does that mean?
I want to buy all of these.
Dude, I'm saving up for all of these.
In fact, I'm going to buy this now.
Reduces the spells, mana cost and recharge time greatly at the cost...
of four health points.
Wait, you mean like every time I shoot?
No way.
Wait, this could be really bad.
Hold on, let me check this first.
In a controlled environment.
Oh, look at that.
But you know what?
If it reduces mana by a hundred...
I could throw this in there.
With that.
So that I always heal, but I always take damage.
In a weird way.
Okay, there's definitely something there.
Something crazy.
But, for now...
Let's just move along.
I have so many ideas for crazy ones.
It's actually wild.
Also, I got completely taken out of my systematic exploration here.
Let's just keep...
You know what?
I'm just going to keep running around in a random walk.
And find some enemies to kill and explore.
At some point, I'll come up on it, I guess.
So this guy right here needs to die immediately.
You know what I need?
Ah, wait, I don't have that spell.
Yo!
Circle of transmogrification.
If I do that on these guys...
When I kill them, they're not going to bleed that shit.
Oh, dude.
I just came up with an insane wand idea.
Check this out.
I put this one on infinite.
Okay?
And then, wherever I shoot...
Everyone's going to get turned into sheep.
And then the shot comes in after.
It doesn't matter how much damage I do.
They just die.
Whoa!
That is crazy.
That's an idea for sure.
Very cool.
Oh, don't go in there.
That's dangerous.
Yo, I'm loving this place up here.
This is insanity.
There's so many spells.
And it's like insane spells, all of them.
And they're all new and exciting.
I'm excited.
What can I say?
I'm very excited.
You know what?
My luck probably says I'm going to find this spell I'm looking for now.
And I won't have enough money.
And I go around finding more enemies to kill.
And then I can't find it again.
I guarantee you that's what's going to happen.
I guarantee it.
Okay.
This is the bottom.
Maybe it's easier to do from left to right.
So now I just keep going along the bottom.
Uh oh.
What is that stuff there?
Snow.
This will also allow us to test how far actually this goes.
Here.
Like horizontally speaking.
Okay.
Then we go up a little.
And then we go left.
This is one way to do it.
And that way we also find all potential enemies to kill.
Kind of stuck.
Keep going left.
It's actually nice that I'm invisible.
I completely forgot that I had that perk.
Okay, we're not there yet.
Oops.
I got to be careful with that.
A spell could fall down like that.
It is actually possible that I made a spell fall down.
And never to be seen again.
Because I did it like that, you know.
Okay, that's the end there.
We go up a little higher.
Maybe to here.
And we keep going.
Oh, is that it?
That's the one.
And look at it.
It only has one use.
Oh man.
We're totally going to be omeguing that one.
Okay.
So, easy to remember now.
It is right at the edge.
It's right at the edge.
There's no way we can miss that now.
And how far from the bottom?
It's like super close.
Awesome.
Now we go collect some money.
And we shall never forget where it is again.
So this area actually goes sort of right and then up again.
So I can't be fooled by this.
This looks like the edge here, but it's not.
Well, it is the edge of this part, but you know what I mean.
Oops.
Any enemies?
Ah.
This is where I was.
What is that one?
We can encourage projectiles.
Is that like, how is that not insane?
Because all I do is projectile.
Actually, it's not.
Yeah, it is.
This is a projectile damage.
That sounds pretty good to me.
Oh, what is that one?
Is that the Giga?
No, that's a white hole.
Oh, I see you there.
So quiet up here suddenly, huh?
I wonder if these guys qualify as angels.
Okay.
What is that one called?
Oh, Gamma.
Okay.
That's actually the capital Gamma then.
Uh-oh.
Oh, shit.
Get rid of him.
It's too risky.
Huh?
Nah, it's not happening.
I do not like the polymorph.
I do like these though.
I can't fucking believe I have infinite healing.
It's actually blowing my mind.
That will never get old.
Holy crap.
There's new music here too.
This is like a legit place.
Wait, where's that electricity?
Also, there's sand here?
Wait, what?
There's a bunch of sand.
Hold on, is there something in the sand?
Man, the teleport is actually so nice for picking up the gold coins.
Is this the rightmost edge?
Also, we're at 35k now.
It's time.
Okay, so my plan with this, because we're definitely running out of enemies here, I want to get the gold one in hopes that I can actually use it forever.
Imagine that with the right...
Omega.
And then using that, I can get so much money that I can buy everything else.
So hopefully that works out the way I think.
Let's see.
We go all the way here.
I believe we go...
Down.
No, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Maybe I am a little bit lost again.
It was all the way to the west.
Like here.
But then it was further down.
No, here it is, here it is.
There we go.
Fuck!
I don't have enough.
I thought it was 35k flat.
Shit.
Oh, that sucks.
God damn it.
Ah, you there.
Come here.
Money, money.
No!
Alright, we got enough.
Nice.
Okay.
Let's see now.
Um, let's put these here.
Let me do this.
So my hope is that with this one...
We are gonna...
Hold on.
Transmures everything in a short radius into gold.
Including walls, creatures and you.
Okay, okay, okay.
We gotta be careful here.
I think we absolutely need to put this on a trigger.
And...
Um...
What else?
I wish I had long distance cast.
Just to be safe here.
There.
And then this one at the end.
So that...
It casts copies of every other...
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I'm scared that this will, uh...
Cast this one and this one at the same time.
So that this one is being cast right where I am.
If this actually kills me...
That...
Hold on.
Maybe I'll try this first.
Just to see what happens.
Okay.
It actually did that.
Holy fuck.
Okay.
Now we gotta be careful.
How do we do this?
I need to actually test...
Exactly how...
I need to really understand how this Omega works.
So let's say I do...
Um...
What's a good test to make?
This one.
So if I shoot this one now...
Oh, wait, this is also spells per cast three.
Let's see here.
Wait, I can't really tell.
Uh, put on...
That one.
No.
Wait.
Um, we can do this easier.
We need something easily visible.
Man, fuck, I don't have any other projectiles.
Wait, I have...
Shit, I don't really have anything that's easily visible here.
I guess I have a teleport.
So if I...
Okay, hold on.
Did that cast it twice?
Hmm.
Makes any hard solid materials within a projectile's range turn into sand.
Okay, so that one could sort of be similar to that, right?
So if I do that and I put it on this...
That's sort of simulating what's happening here, right?
And to make it even more clear...
We're gonna put on...
Uh...
So this is a modifier.
I want to shoot this and then when it impacts, I want it to modify a chainsaw.
So the question is, does anything happen where I'm standing right now?
That's the test.
It does!
Okay, but it could be because I'm casting three spells per cast here.
So really what we need to do is test it on a wand that only casts one spell per cast.
Which is a little annoying right now because I have to get rid of a bunch of spells.
Let's do it.
Also, I just threw down the fucking thing I needed and it's fine, it's fine.
Okay.
No!
I don't have enough mana, that sucks.
Maybe that's gonna be enough?
Fuck, I... Oh no, man.
Uh...
Shit.
This is bad, this is really bad.
You know what?
Hmm...
How can I fucking test this properly?
Uh...
Okay, so obviously, okay, so this casts three spells per cast.
So when I click the button, it's gonna cast this one.
Which then, at impact, casts these two.
But it's also at the same time gonna cast this one.
Which casts a copy of every spell in my wand.
And every spell here could simply mean that one, that one, that one.
And not just that one, even because this is technically only one spell, because...
This is like an umbrella spell for these two, if you know what I mean.
But if I were to do...
This!
What then?
Yeah, okay.
Wait, unless I'm misunderstanding something here, hold on.
If I shoot from here...
Oh, hold on now, hold on.
No, it's definitely impacting where I'm standing too.
Oh, I feel like this is a dangerous spell to experiment with, guys.
I may not do it.
I'm too scared.
I'm scared of it just killing me.
I'm scared of this just going, that's it.
You know, we're done.
What I really need is a long distance cast, basically.
Long distance cast.
Yeah, I need long distance cast.
Unless I...
Fuck.
Yeah, whatever.
I give up.
We gotta try this somewhere else.
I don't have the mental capacity to not die right now, basically.
Let's get our old one back.
That was that one.
Oh, hold on.
Maybe I can use some of this.
Increases the rego.
We don't want to increase it.
Speed.
Okay.
I think this is fine.
What did I have on this one?
It was teleport, wasn't it?
Teleport.
Oh, wait.
Here we go.
Teleport.
That one.
Oh, you know what?
This one could be used for this.
Let's say you just remove two of your wands.
So that you guarantee that you can do this safely.
You know what I mean?
So you put in a spark bolt.
With the touch of gold.
On another wand.
And then you use seida on your number one wand.
So that you guarantee that's the only thing that's getting cast here.
You know what I mean?
Oh, wait.
No.
A random spell.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no.
This could be bad.
Random is bad.
Nope.
Forget what I said.
It's a bad idea.
Bad idea.
This one I'm also scared of.
Touch of smoke.
It's the same shit.
I don't want to turn into smoke.
Seems like a bad idea, guys.
Yeah.
Wait.
There's something wrong with my...
Oh, this one's missing.
Right.
Where did I have it?
Here?
I think so.
Yeah.
This is what I had.
Yep.
Alright, let's move on.
I mean, we're doing well.
Let me just check this.
That is doing things as expected.
Teleport is doing things as expected.
Everything is as expected.
Beautiful.
Alright.
Well, if we get some more money, we know where to go.
Because there's all kinds of crazy spells here.
Yeah.
Let's keep going up.
If we can.
Doesn't seem like this is the edge.
Doesn't it?
Is there anything up here?
Oh, there's actually... Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Yo, hold on now.
This looks different.
Oh, this is like...
Look at this.
This is the vault textures.
Right?
Uh oh.
Those things can fuck right off.
I swear to God.
We got to do something about those.
I wish I had more slots to store my spells so I could just have a...
transmogrification on my fourth one so I could deal with those guys in a safe manner.
That would be lovely.
This place is breaking my brain right now.
Did I just kill that guy with a black hole?
Usually that doesn't hurt them.
Shit.
I mean, we can farm some gold here.
No problem.
Oh, he died, he died, he died.
One thing I've noticed, there's no wands here.
It's like, there's spells.
No wands.
Isn't that interesting?
Very odd.
Oh, we're back down here now.
Wait, where did I just come from?
Ouch!
How dare you?
Wait, where the hell was I just now?
Was I up here?
I was, okay.
This is so odd.
I hate to say this, guys, but...
this place almost feels like a...
like it's bugged.
I know if I ask you, you're probably gonna be like, nope, not a bug, but...
fucking hell.
It looks like a bug to me.
Or like, something ain't right, like the world is corrupted or something.
Will you stop hurting me?
Like, look at this stuff.
It looks like something is missing from this area.
You know what I mean?
Like, something's missing.
Getting lots of money, though.
Not as many spells here as in the other area.
What is that one?
Hold on now.
Oh my god.
Null shot.
Wait a minute, is that the one I already have?
Oh, it is!
It just looked different for some reason.
I think the white background is messing with me a little bit.
Was that honey?
Or was that yellow stuff?
Hey.
Hand over your money.
Man, that's a damage.
Man, I want to buy all these.
Funny thing is, they all have the same price.
It's like 35,000 something.
Oh no.
Sir...
Bye-bye.
It's like a fever dream up here.
Alright, let's keep going up.
There's gotta be more.
Maybe not.
It does feel like it's sort of going up and to the right, you know?
Hey!
What's up, guys?
That looked really funny.
Space Invaders.
What the hell?
Wait a minute.
Wait, where am I now?
Oh yeah, yeah, wait, what?
I'm so confused.
Am I back all the way down again?
No, I'm not.
Ground just... this is...
No, this is not the same area.
I am so lost.
Nothing over there.
Well, let me go back up again.
I have no clue where I am.
Try going more left.
Oh!
Here we go!
Oh yeah, here we go!
Look at this stuff!
Fuck off.
Yeah, man.
What the hell?
Barrens... oh, that all burns away.
The soil is burning.
Oh, what the hell, man?
I have... I have not a lot of time to stand on this before it's gone.
That's very funny.
Uh-oh.
Stand on the sand.
Sand is safe.
Almost.
Okay.
I have no clue what's going on right now, guys, but this is fucking crazy.
We are just ascending the world.
In fact, we're approaching the moon all the time.
Have you noticed?
Oh, man, I need to stay in the center.
I get it now.
I need to keep using my compass here.
My compass.
Look, the moon is almost straight above right now.
That's perfect.
I wanted to go to the moon anyway.
Did he die?
I am fucking razor focused.
Because there's polymorphine left and right here.
I need to be Omega careful.
I'm getting good money here.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
We are some kind of little machine.
No.
I was polymorph to Lenocki.
Goddamn.
Well, that was bound to happen at some point.
Too much goddamn polymorphine.
Man, what a run.
Let's see the stats.
16 hours.
Damn.
64 places visited.
Look at this.
Record 25 before that.
4000 and that's twice my normal amount.
Wait, what do you mean max HP 10?
The fuck is that?
No, no, no.
It was 2000 something.
Is that because I was polymorph at the end and that's how I died?
That's fucking annoying.
You absolute fucker.
Put that number at 2400.
That's a lie.
Eight orbs.
I wonder what this means.
What is it with the orbs collected?
Streak zero.
Best one.
Right.
Total deaths 90.
Total wins one.
Damn.
Let's see progress.
Look at all the enemies I found now.
I'm almost finding everything.
That's super satisfying.
Look how many new spells I discovered in this run.
Holy shit.
Null shot.
Necromancy.
Oh yeah, look.
All these are new.
Wait, what's happening?
Oh, okay.
Let's see.
Okay, you know what?
This sound is annoying me right now.
Are they fighting each other?
What's happening?
Idiots.
Stop it.
Bro, that was fun, man.
That was a crazy run!
Okay, so look at this stone right here.
You see that?
There's three eyes.
It could mean west, center, east.
Right?
West, center, east.
And it's the same three eyes that appear in the fungal caverns.
When you use the demon eye.
So there's something going on there.
I need to think about that.
WASD.
Also, there's some writing underneath.
Wait, is this giving me a translation?
WASD?
No.
There's one, two, three, four, five, six symbols down below.
I need a primer.
I need a cipher of some kind.
Something that will allow me to translate this.
In fact, this is the only place in the game so far, I think.
Where there's actual letters, you know, from the human race.
Also, it has become night.
Man, oh!
Oh, I feel renewed.
That was awesome.
What a run.
And you know what?
We have magic missile.
So we can do things like this now.
In the very beginning.
Sixteen hour run.
In fact, sixteen hours is...
Let me think.
It's like one-sixth of my entire playtime in this game.
One-sixth, dude.
Or like one-seventh, something like that.
Like in between that.
It's very substantial.
Ah!
Need mana.
There we go.
Yoink!
Fuck yeah.
And I have pheromone potion.
Interesting.
Okay, I need to immediately remove this from that slot because I will attempt to teleport with that keybind.
Because I'm so used to teleporting now.
It's gonna be so weird not having teleport.
And not being able to dig everywhere.
So hold on.
Let me actually think about things a little more here now.
F.
I.
I mean, obviously it's teaching me how to play the game here.
I get that.
But maybe there's also a translation layer somewhere here.
You gotta be able to...
I'm assuming here, of course, that those symbols in the game, because they appear again and again, actually has some meaning.
I basically have the same wand as I had last run.
Right now it's just a lot slower.
Think about it.
It's the same shit.
I'll take that.
Thank you.
Twenty-five of them.
Bam.
Also, I am not fire immune.
Let's keep that in mind.
So the pheromone potion is nice, but I may actually empty it for water.
Just because it is actually that important.
I'll put this somewhere where I can pick it up again.
Maybe I'll make a little...
pool here.
This is a bit of a waste.
Yeah, it is.
I'm gonna find a natural pool for it.
What's that?
Flammoxium.
Oh, there we go.
That's what I needed.
Because now I can empty this, and then I can still keep my pheromone.
Yeah, just put the flammoxium over here.
Nobody cares.
Put it there, and then piece them over here.
Alabina, don't overflow.
Nice.
I was just about to try and teleport again.
No such thing now.
Okay, so I...
The fact that I know that I can get more perks than the ones in this part of the world, I guess...
is actually changing my whole perspective on things, you know?
And the fact that I can get so much more money later on makes me think that if I find shitty perks that I really don't want, I shouldn't take one of them.
I can save them for later.
It's fine.
Like, I will get the money.
You know?
Oh, look at that.
Oh, dude.
We're gonna get more money like this.
Oh, no.
They burned to death.
But actually, that's fine too.
Yeah.
We're chilling.
Ouch!
Bastard.
I'm not firing here.
Just do not run into fire.
Ouch!
Man, they're getting some good hits in on me.
You.
I missed.
I'm getting a little too brazen here.
Fuck!
He blew that one off course.
Shit.
This is the ultimate duel.
Hey!
What did he say to that?
Awesome.
Is that?
That's chaotic polymorphine.
That is no bueno.
We do not enjoy chaotic polymorphine.
I'm gonna use my tablet more just because it gives more money.
Or does it?
That one didn't.
Why is that?
That one did.
Whoops.
That's gonna be a little bit problematic.
Let me wet myself.
Got it.
Nice.
Money, money, money, money.
This is actually a little bit.
That's fine.
We're fine.
Holy crap.
There it is.
Hey, horta and hamises.
Oh!
It actually ended up killing you!
Ow!
I'm being a little greedy here, I realize.
Ah!
I'm playing terribly.
I'm too greedy.
Hot delivery!
Yo, that was awesome.
Fucking drive by throw or fall by throw.
I can get in there.
Why did I get in there?
My eyes did not wander over here to check what was in there.
My brain was like, we can make a hole there.
We should make a hole there.
Shit!
We're actually almost dead.
I think I'm playing a little too fast and loose here.
Because I'm used to having heals.
I need to get rid of that way of thinking.
So I want my tablet.
Where'd he go?
There it is.
Wait, did he kill something down here?
Must have fallen on someone, I think.
I could go in now.
Let me just explore this little region first.
Just real quick, you know?
He's gonna burn.
Water myself.
Grab the grab.
Oh shit!
Fuck!
No!
Oh shit!
Okay, we're leaving.
Yeah, let's just leave, let's just leave.
That's getting a little out of hand.
Dude, we're fucking talking now.
Chain bolt!
My favorite in this part of the game.
And look at that!
Would you look at that?
It's fire immunity.
We're back in business.
Just like that.
Nothing can stop us.
Let's see, no, that's a shitty recharge on that.
Ooh.
Oh wait, this cost...
Oh, that's a shitty one.
Wow, what a one.
Dude, I have no good wants.
Okay, this one is maybe okay.
Explosion.
Triplicate bolt.
There's so many options.
I think I kind of want this one, guys.
Just a good old luminous drill.
Oh, that runs out fast.
That's probably the best bet for that one.
In a pinch.
This one, delayed spell cast.
Double.
I mean, that one is not bad either.
No, that's terrible.
I think this is my best bet for that.
Yeah, we're using that for main damage.
And we have digging.
That's okay.
I think I will buy this one as well.
As well as that one.
There's two delayed spell cast here.
I'll take explosion as well.
Let's take one of these and that one.
Like, why wouldn't I take all of this, right?
That's what I'm thinking.
A static magical phenomenon that casts three extra spells after a short while.
I think we're okay.
We could make someone angry here.
I do have my luminous drill and chain bolt combo.
You know?
That one could be the way to go here.
Make a little something something.
He's not going to get angry when I dig here, right?
Hold on.
Let's see how feasible this is.
If he gets angry, we're kind of fucked.
No, if he gets angry, we just leave.
We try to get out.
And then we use the tablet technique.
This is the ultimate way of dealing with it, guys.
If you haven't seen this miraculous method before, get ready to feast your eyes.
This is the most genius galaxy brain shit you have ever witnessed.
Alright.
I need to make it a little bit bigger, though, so I can fit in there.
Do I fit?
Oh, I do fit.
Let me just double check.
Everything is in working order.
Yeah, sort of.
Hold on.
What?
Stop, stop.
Why do you... Oh, there we go.
Okay, I see, I see.
Yes!
It needs to be a little more reliable, so let me just make it a little bigger.
Something like that.
Okay, now we just got to make him mad.
Oh, he's so mad now.
Yo, Stuart!
There he comes.
Come here.
And while he's doing that, I can just dig a little bit here.
Just while we're waiting.
Come on, Stuart.
Come over here.
Seems like he doesn't even know I'm here, which is kind of weird.
That means I can kill him from this side.
Unless he finally decides to come over here.
I could go out and lure him in, but I'm afraid if I do that, I'm going to fumble it and not die.
I'm going to place this in time and he's going to kill me.
So I'm just playing this ultra safe.
I don't want to fumble things.
I tend to panic in situations like this.
So the more prepared I can be...
A bit more.
What do you think about that, Stuart?
You mad now, bro?
Oh, yeah.
He's trying to leave now.
He doesn't know where it's coming from.
He's so confused.
Oh, he's got a sense.
He senses me in the wall.
I'm in the walls, baby.
Haunting you.
Come closer.
He's actually being nice.
He's walking away to let me regenerate some mana.
He knows that I have a shitty wand.
There we go, baby.
You ain't shit.
Give me your money.
And there it is.
We can now come back here and change our wands.
Easy peasy, lemon squeezy.
And now...
Hold on, instead of...
Can I just get rid of that?
There we go.
Now make a hole.
It's not much, but it's honest work.
How come he doesn't get mad at me for this?
Not quite yet.
There we go.
Made it.
Fuck yeah.
That was so satisfying.
Let's go kill some fools.
Oh yeah, I'm firing immune.
What the fuck is that?
Hello?
Breakwork?
What?
Look at that.
It has writing on it too.
Oh no, it's everything burning now.
What's that?
Something's happening.
Oh!
Thanks?
Wait, why is the sound so low now?
You hear it?
Wait.
Oh.
We're inside the thing.
Look at it.
It's the same.
We have been miniaturized.
I think.
Listen to the sound.
Is that gonna take me back?
No way.
Okay.
Wait, what?
Oh no.
Oh no, what have I done?
Oh, wait.
Huh?
Okay, that's weird as hell.
What is...
Okay.
I have a feeling this happened because I did something special last run.
Yo, that's insane.
Look at this.
I got a wand out of it and it's kind of crazy wand too.
Hold on, I kind of want to go back.
Is that just gonna be here?
That's so weird.
I'm so intrigued.
This game just keeps throwing new shit at me.
What the actual F?
I mean, blowing lands on my beloved and all that, but...
That's really nice.
I prefer that right now.
Yeah.
Delayed spell cast.
I could double spell it.
Something like that, maybe.
I mean, it looks a little silly, but there's no reason not to do it, I guess.
It's just more damage.
Or that, even.
You know, like there's no reason not to do that.
Maybe it's a little silly.
Yeah, whatever.
This is insane.
I feel like I'm already in a super good position.
What's over here?
It's a little bit scuff digging, isn't it?
After what we're used to.
Oh wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
Triplicate bolt.
Can dig.
That's a way better digger.
But then again, luminous drill does dig through everything, so let's just keep that, actually.
Yeah, it may be a little slower, but at least we can go anywhere.
And when it's soft material like this, I easily get through.
It's actually fine.
I feel like I've become professional at Noisa at this point.
I am a professional Noisa gamer.
I don't want to get through there.
There's too much digging.
I can't believe this is just here.
Like, what even is this?
Oh, I kind of...
Yo.
I'm escaping.
Why didn't I try this before?
Yo, am I going to be able to traverse the world as a miniature wizard now?
Oh, listen, the sound is coming back.
Oh.
Say what now?
I mean, I can dig through that, right?
I can, but it's going to take a while.
That's not something I'm willing to do.
Let me try the other side.
Yo.
Wait a minute.
Two things.
One, there's blood in here, right?
And there was a bone.
Makes me think, maybe I need to...
fill it up with more blood.
And something will happen.
And also, there's text in the background.
Look at that.
This is like the...
Wait, is it?
Like the inverse note sign.
Oh, everything is on top!
It's like reverse, isn't it?
Hold on.
Actually, no, it's kind of hard to tell.
I feel like I've seen this symbol, but upside down, you know?
Let me see what's up here.
What even is this place, man?
It's just called Brickwork.
Oh.
Hold on.
What's happening here?
Oh, not much it seems.
Eh.
Yeah.
That's such a cool effect, the way the audio just gets...
muted like that, you know?
Alright, let's get out.
Okay, can I...
Can I transport this?
I can't kick it.
What if I dig it?
Ooh.
Oh, I'll just leave it.
I'll just leave it like that for now.
I don't want to destroy it.
Alright.
What else is going on?
Nice fireworks.
Honestly, kind of refreshing to be back in a not so hectic and all over the place type of play style, you know?
This is more down to earth.
I actually prefer this a little bit slower pace.
Like, it is fun to go fast and stuff, but...
like, if I have a preference, it's probably to go a little slower.
Guys?
Round the corner.
What
do we got over here?
I could dig through, but no, I'm too lazy.
We need like an energy orb.
Energy sphere.
To really get through those thick places.
That was a bit risky.
Okay, let's grab some water.
I think I hear the portal.
Hey.
Alright.
It's actually a really respectable wand I have here.
Another portal down there.
Let me grab this gold.
494 in the bank.
Also, let me just point out here that I haven't lost a single HP point.
Actually, it's just a single HP.
Oh.
It's not jinxed actually.
I have wand.
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, you shoot my...
Hey.
Oh no.
There goes the jinx.
I want to get in there.
There we go.
Ooh.
Some light is nice.
I think I like it more than I like the current one I had.
Now it just pushes it further into the ground with the luminous drill.
So you don't want to be digging for gold like that.
Look at that one.
That's a funny looking wand.
Two luminous drills with timers.
600 mana max but very low mana charge speed.
Let's see how it fares.
Horrible.
Yikes.
That's a yikes from me.
What?
500.
Oh!
Shit, I didn't even see you.
Where are you?
Oh.
Don't even think about it.
I think I got you there.
Nope.
Shit.
You absolute piece of shit.
Okay, let's chill.
Come on.
Six seconds.
There we go.
What an annoying spell.
Holy crap.
That is actually the worst.
Oh wait, we're in the fungal area.
That actually makes a lot of sense.
Let's risk it for the biscuit.
We have 100 HP.
Most importantly, we have the knowledge to survive.
We're like Bear Grylls at this point.
I'm not afraid to drink my own pee.
There's a wand there.
A bunch of eggs.
No thanks.
Oh, another wand.
A digging bolt.
Fuck yeah.
Thanks.
That's cool.
I appreciate that, my man.
I want to go back to the fungal caverns, please.
Is that at all possible?
Man, how far did I teleport?
Watch this.
Ah shit, I missed it.
Would have been cool though.
Got it.
Ah, lava.
An egg.
I shall grab it.
The air feels extremely humid.
Well, yeah.
It's like a rainforest in here.
On a science goal.
God, I hate those totes.
Give me the money.
We've got a man in there.
You know what?
The nice thing about this combo is that if I hit them with the...
that one, they're going to get knocked back.
Especially these guys that do melee attacks.
Really nice.
Okay, we've got multiple wands.
No, actually just one wand.
Let's see what else we got here.
Oh, should I get high?
We could get high.
We could get drunk and high at the same...
Dude, let's try that.
I'm not even kidding.
Maybe there's some kind of thing that happens.
If you're drunk and high at the same time.
Sounds glorious to me.
But first we gotta find...
Okay, that's a bit...
Oh, this is way too many explosions.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Get rid of this.
Get rid of that.
Oopsie-dopesie.
Gotcha.
And you there.
Would you like a surprise gift?
He doesn't want the gift.
Unstable teleport...
Oh, actually, I want to pick that up.
Let's leave the tablet here for now.
Uh-oh.
Oopsie-daisy.
Get some water in there.
Oh, no.
There we go.
Oh, not this guy.
Hey, watch this.
Come
here.
Successful.
Now we wait for that asset.
Beautiful stuff.
Oh, shit, I didn't even see you there.
Oh, no!
Motherfucker!
I'm stuck!
I can't move!
Are you kidding me?
All the little stupid pixels of dirt.
I was stuck.
Fuck you, Robotikuta.
Mother crabber.
Wow.
Well, that's a bummer.
That was such a good start, though.
Okay, I'm actually gonna stop now, because it's been four and a half hours.
And I need to...
I'm actually...
Yeah, I'm playing way too many games, man.
I need to calm down here.
Whoops.
Go over there.
Gotta get up for work tomorrow.
What's up, people?
How about that run, huh?
Was that the craziest run of all time, or what?
For me, at least.
Maybe it's nothing to you guys, I don't know.
I mean, not this current one.
But the one before that.
Hold on, I'm gonna put on some...
relaxing music.
I need to get back into...
some more Hollow Knight music.
It's too good.
Nightmare?
Already a pro noiter gamer?
I feel like what I just did there wasn't very pro.
That was kind of amateur.
I put myself in a bad spot.
Especially because I didn't even see the guy waiting on the other side.
Like, how blind can you be?
If I had seen him, I wouldn't have just gone in like that.
That was stupid of me.
I gotta open my eyes.
Definitely try Nightmare?
Oh, you mean the game mode.
I thought you meant it was a nightmare.
I feel like the game is already hard enough, isn't it?
The 16-hour run was great.
Have you considered using onlyones.com?
That sounds...
Is that a sexual website?
Onlyones?
For us to be able to see you once all the time.
What do you mean?
What is that?
I don't know about that.
Are you taking the piss?
Taking 20 poly baths is not pro at all?
Well, I think it's more pro than taking only one and dying, isn't it?
Think about it this way.
I took 20 poly baths and lived.
What do you think about that?
It's a streamer mod so chat can see your inventory.
Oh!
Well, hell yeah.
Definitely.
What?
Of course.
That sounds awesome.
You have reached a record HP of 10.
That's something.
True.
I mean, if you think about it, it's kind of hard to end with 10 HP.
Like a maximum of 10 HP.
So hold on.
Onlyones.
Oh, streamer ones.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I'm going to set that up for next time, guys.
For sure.
I didn't even realize that was a thing.
That sounds cool.
You need another mod to disable mod restrictions if you use it, though.
Or things will change in the game.
Oh, really?
In what way?
The only problem with Onlyones is not to mistype if by habit.
I don't know.
I don't know what you mean.
Spoiler, but things change?
Oh, really?
A couple places don't spawn if you have mods.
Oh.
So should I use this or not?
It does sound very convenient for a viewer if you're able to see my inventory and all that.
But if it's going to change things...
But you said I could download a mod that wouldn't have it change things?
Only if you get disabled mod restrictions.
Okay.
Oh, you mistype F instead of the mod for you.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
And it is sort of close to each other on the keyboard.
Limital roar, but the mod won't change anything like significant, right?
It's just for the viewers.
That's the way I understand it.
They
will disable Steam achievements.
I don't care about Steam achievements anyway.
I always have all achievements turned off because they always distract me.
I hate achievements.
So that's totally not a problem for me.
Unrelated.
Latest Twitch app update is trash?
Twitch app update?
Oh, you mean on the phone?
I have no idea how that works.
I've never used Twitch on the phone.
I feel like most things on the phone suck.
I hate using phone apps for things.
But I can totally understand.
It wouldn't surprise me if it sucked.
It was fine.
Now it sucks.
Oh, man.
Hopefully they'll change it back to what it was.
Calling people on the phone sucks too.
I use my fridge.
You also play Skyrim on the fridge?
Wait a minute.
Every time people type lol, this fucking hamster comes up with the little rotating blade above it.
It just makes me laugh, man.
Like, why has that been replaced?
God damn it.
You know what that reminds me of?
Reminds me of that dude sitting there eating chips, just looking at the camera.
What do you mean?
It's like the same thing.
I also feel like the angle of that hamster is the same thing when you give a phone to an old person and they take a picture of themselves.
Exactly, lolvie.
That's the one.
I love that dude so much.
Very based.
That's just hilarious.
You know what?
So, sometimes I can't stop laughing when I'm...
So, I browse YouTube a lot, right?
And I watch random videos.
And lately I've been watching these Anthony Bourdain videos.
No wait, is that his name?
Hold on.
It's the guy with the stock cubes.
No no, that's Marco Pierre.
So he has like a whole series on YouTube on different recipes, right?
But he's being sponsored by Nore.
So he's using these Nore stock cubes in every recipe.
And you can just tell that he wouldn't normally use this, but he's just doing it for the sponsorship.
So all the comments is some variation on a joke with like stock cubes.
That shit fucking makes me laugh, man.
There are so many small things like that.
Ah man, that was a bit unrelated, but yeah.
I love memes.
I love potatoes.
Deliver the potatoes?
Wait, which potatoes?
What potatoes are you speaking of, sir?
Am I supposed to deliver potatoes?
Tell me about the potatoes.
The pole?
Oh, there was a pole, mate?
Maybe the mod that did it is not here anymore.
Let's see.
Will Oliver die and lose his Godrun today?
Oh, I see.
Okay.
So yeah, I can definitely give potatoes.
Choose outcome.
Yes, death is inevitable.
Complete prediction?
Yes.
There it is.
The potatoes have been distributed amongst the people.
Also, thank you, Raffina, for subscribing once again with Prime.
Place diorite on the MC server for you today.
I really appreciate that, man.
Is that like one more diorite on the diorite cube?
Similar to, you know, the little towers of rocks that hikers make when they are out hiking?
You put like a little diorite cube on top.
I appreciate it, Raffina.
Is it Raffinha or Raffinha?
Because you have double A's on there.
Can but not paid.
It's paid now.
The debt is paid.
Enjoy the potatoes.
Blessed be.
Time to make fries.
I mean, yeah.
Also, put one of them in the microwave.
I promise it's good.
Just oil it and salt it first.
I'm still high from that run.
Oh, man.
Good stream.
Thanks for still keeping with Neutze.
Man, I'm gonna keep playing it until I feel like playing something else.
It's that simple.
And I still... I'm still having lots of fun with it.
But even though I'm still having lots of fun with it, I may actually start another game soon.
Maybe in a couple of streams.
Something new.
And then come back to Neutze once in a while.
The game has become a little insane at this moment.
It's like...
Oh, man.
How many hours do I have in this game now?
124 hours.
124.
That's still quite a lot.
I think I had around 200 in Minecraft, didn't I?
That was a long game.
And I intend to come back to that as well.
I'm way behind on Voss.
Just came back for a chat.
Neither?
Oh, okay.
How do I pronounce it correctly then, Raffina?
If you can even explain that in text.
Hope you don't get Terraria-like burnout again.
I didn't get burned out on Terraria.
I just didn't enjoy it at the end.
It's just not the game for me.
It was fun in the beginning.
But after I reached a certain milestone in the game, I just didn't have any fun with it at all after that.
It wasn't burnout.
It was simply...
It just wasn't for me.
That type of game.
I'm Brazilian.
That's how Raffinha is pronounced.
Haffinia.
Oh.
Haffinia?
Hopefully it's a little better.
That's close.
Okay, thanks.
Noita is way more addicting and replayable long-term.
I mean, it depends on the person, right?
Like, some may say it's the opposite, and that's totally fine as well.
Every game is just not for everyone, and that's just how it is.
I was skeptical if you would like Noita before you started.
It's a hit or miss.
I can imagine that.
I feel the same way about Noita as I do about Rainworld in that regard.
That it's a game you will either love or maybe hate, you know?
Because it's so difficult, but it's just so rewarding as well at the same time.
It's also very different than most games.
Like, both Rainworld and Noita.
I kind of grouped those two games together in my mind a lot.
Portuguese.
Okay, I'm gonna release a... I'm gonna put up the next video for Prey.
And then it's actually time for me to go to bed.
Yeah.
Thank you so much for watching, guys.
Let's raid someone.
Let's send you over.
Let's see who's streaming this game.
There's Let's Suffer together.
Let's try someone new.
How about...
We're gonna do someone named...
Uh, who's here?
There's so many people playing this game.
It's actually...
This game is really popular.
Isn't it?
We're gonna street... We're gonna raid Kiali, of course.
May the gods of Noita grant me a godrun.
Here we go.
Have fun, guys.
Thanks for watching.
See you around.